al
al
[Music]
[Música]
Ok here we Go the here
Ok here we Go
for you if you know the
the here per for you if you know the
words you can Jo put your hands together
words you can Jo put your hands Together
ifap as we take you through this monkey
ifap as we take you through this monkey
[Music]
[Música]
rykey
rykey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
He's the leader of the bunch you know
He's the leader of the bunch you know
him well He's Finally back to Kick some ta
him well He's Finally back to Kick some
his Coconut gum can Fire And sps If
ta his Coconut gum can Fire And sps If
he shoots you It's gna hurt He's bigger
he shoots you It's gna hurt He's bigger
faster and stronger too He's the First
faster and stronger too He's the First
member of the dk Crew
member of the dk Crew
dkey
dkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
dk  Donkey
dk Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
here Donkey
here
Donkey k
Donkey Donkey k
got so Listen up to She can shink in
got so Listen up to She can shink in
size to suit her She quick and When She
size to suit her She quick and When She
needs to be She can flo through the air
needs to be She can flo through the air
and Climb up tre if you choose
and Climb up tre if you choose
her wrong with sk H She's
her wrong with sk H She's
cool
cool
d Donkey Kong
d Donkey Kong
d Donkey Kong is here
d Donkey Kong is here
d Donkey
d Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is here he has no Style
Kong Donkey Kong is here he has no Style
he has no Grace
he has no
this Kong has a funny Face he can hand
Grace this Kong has a funny Face he can
when he needs to and stretch his
hand when he needs to and stretch his
Arms out Just for you inflate him
Arms out Just for you inflate him
[Music]
[Música]
Donkey Kong iskey
Donkey Kong iskey
K He's Back Again
K He's Back Again
[Music]
[Música]
and with his Jetpack G with his pistols
and with his Jetpack G with his pistols
out He's One tough he'll Make You Smile
out He's One tough he'll Make You Smile
when he Plays but klin beware He's after
when he Plays but klin beware He's after
[Music]
[Música]
youy Donkey Kong is
youy Donkey Kong is
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally he's here for
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally he here for
you It's the last member of the dk Crew this
you It's The Last member of the dk Crew
K so strong it isn't funny can make
this K so strong it isn't funny can make
a klin Cry out for mmy can't pick up a b
a klin Cry out for mmy can't pick up a b
with relative ease makes crushing Rocks
with relative ease makes crushing Rocks
seem such a breeze he May move Slow he ca
seem such a breeze he May move Slow he
n't jump High but this comes One Hell
can't jump High but this comes One Hell
Of A gu Come on cranky take it to the
Of A gu Come on cranky take it to the
fridge
fridge
[Music]
[Música]
walnuts peanuts pineapple smells grapes
walnuts peanuts pineapple smells grapes
melons oranges and coconut shell Oh yeah
melons oranges and Coconut shell Oh yeah
walnuts peanut pineapple
walnuts peut pineapple
smells melons oranges and coconut
smells melons oranges and Coconut
[Music]
[Música]
good afternoon how are we doing family
buenas tardes qué tal estamos familia
How are we doing Well I have to
Qué tal estamos Bueno pues tengo que
make this special connection because
hacer esta conexión especial porque han
things have happened and the truth is
pasado cosas y la verdad me acaba de
something just came to me that is absolutely
llegar algo que es absolutamente
impressive something just
impresionante
came to me that is
acaba de llegar algo que es
absolutely impressive how sad it is how
absolutamente impresionante de la pena
sad it is
que da de la pena que da
really m a m  people things and
realmente m a m la gente las cosas y las
shortcomings the little problems that they have
carencias los problemillas que tengan
that they solve them as they can
que lo vayan solucionando como puedan
but yes it is
pero sí que es
strong man the sex necro a kiss what
fuerte hombre la sex necro un beso qué
are these great songs that load the march
son estos temazos que se carga la marcha
a lot of march let's see this schedule is a
mucha marcha a ver este horario es un
little strange but it's that I have to go to
poco raro pero es que me tengo que ir a
the gym at 5 and after the gym
5 al gimnasio y después del gimnasio
I have to do some things with the kid
tengo que hacer unas cosas con el niño
so I don't even know if I'll come
entonces Ni siquiera sé si vendré hoy
here tonight because I have to I do
por la noche por aquí porque tengo
n't know I would like to make a
que no sé me gustaría hacer un un vídeo
powerful video on the main channel a good
potente en el canal principal un un buen
video like to talk about the Dana issue
vídeo o sea tratar el tema de la Dana
but a good video with information
pero un buen vídeo con información
discarding hoaxes and things like that I mean a well
descartar bulos y cosas así O sea un
done video I would like to make a
vídeo currado me gustaría hacer un vídeo
well done video on the Dana issue so I'll
currado sobre el tema de la Dana así que
see if I come here it's just that I don't
ya veré si me vengo para acá es que no
know if I'm going to do it I don't know if I'm going to do it
sé si lo voy voy a hacer No sé si lo voy
okay I mean I'm
a hacer vale o sea me lo estoy
considering it because I think I think it
planteando porque creo que creo que
would be Cool and Cool let's see if you understand me
sería Guay e Guay a ver si me entendéis
ideal ideal let's use that word
ideal ideal vamos a usar esa palabra
better
mejor
okay ideal to have a good video eh with
vale ideal tener un vídeo bien eh con
good information on the main channel I
una buena información en el principal o
mean we're covering it here every
sea lo estamos cubriendo aquí todos los
day No but like  like Super very crazy
días No pero en plan como Super muy loco
now this information Now the other
ahora esta información Ahora la otra
then there is information already from which
luego hay informaciones ya de las que
we have taken videos that are discarded no
hemos sacado vídeos que se descartan no
then I think it would be interesting
entonces m creo que sería interesante
interesting okay it could be very
interesante vale que puede ser muy
unfortunate to say that it could be Cool I think it would
desafortunado decir que puede ser Guay
be
creo que sería
interesting to have a video in
interesante tener un un vídeo en
conditions, I mean a video in
condiciones o sea un vídeo en
conditions with everything well stipulated let's
condiciones con todo bien estipulado a
see but this really I can I want to
ver pero esto realmente yo puedo Quiero
try something eh let's
probar una cosa eh
see good whatever Well then I'll start to
ver buen da igual Bueno luego me pongo a
investigate No no it's that I have the
investigar No no es que tengo aquí la la
GoPro connected here because yesterday I
gopro conectada por el tema de que ayer
recorded the video of delp with the GoPro calla a
grabé el vídeo delp con la gopro cala un
kiss gorgeous how are you and I say it
beso guapísima cómo estás y digo se
can be used as a Webcam too but well
puede usar de Webcam también pero bueno
now is not the time to start
ahora no es momento de de ponerme a
doing tests or investigating because I only have
hacer pruebas investigar porque tengo
an hour and a half I only have an
una hora y media apenas apenas tengo una
hour and a half to be here with you
hora y media para estar aquí con ustedes
and tell you what what's going on
y contaros lo que lo que tal
eh very strong what just happened okay they have
eh muy fuerte lo que acaba de pasar vale
leaked it to me I have put it on
me lo han filtrado lo he puesto en
Twitter
Twitter
and well I'll tell you what it is and then we'll
y bueno os digo lo que es y luego lo
see okay when people start coming in
vemos vale cuando vaya entrando la gente
but Tania was direct I don't know what she
pero Tania estaba directo no sé de qué
was talking about she was talking about me
estaría hablando estaría hablando de mí
I suppose not
Supongo no
Lili Hi Javi I'm studying
Lili Hola Javi estoy estudiando la
to be a  meteorologist I've been
carrera para ser meteorólogo yevo
analyzing what happened and I've made
analizando lo que ha pasado y he hecho
some inter compilations if you
algunas recopilaciones inter si me lo
can send it to me and that video that I want to
puedes mandar y ese vídeo que quiero
make can help me stormy if you
hacer me puede ayudar stormy si me lo
want to send it to me send it to my
quieres mandar mándamelo al md de
Instagram dm and tell me I'm the one who sent you
Instagram y dime soy la que te mand el
the message the super chat in the live
el mensaje el super chat en el directo
not so that I know it's you because I
no para que yo sepa que eres tú porque
have
tengo
Tania was live
Tania estaba en directo
talking I would be talking about jav
hablando estaría hablando de jav
oliveira
oliveira
No yes I was talking about Javi oliveira and
No sí estaba hablando de Javi oliveira y
he leaked his WhatsApp by accident as she is
a filtrado su WhatsApp sin querer como
so intelligent and so
es tan inteligente y tan
smart she was talking about Javi
espabilada estaba hablando de Javi
oliveira and he leaked his WhatsApp and it
oliveira y ha filtrado su WhatsApp y
turns out that
resulta queene
in
en el
WhatsApp there are two groups
WhatsApp dos grupos
organized to talk about Javi oliveira
organizados para hablar de Javi oliveira
okay Eh I don't get to see the participants because of the quality
vale Eh no llego a ver por la calidad
but obviously one
los participantes pero evidentemente una
is the one not that one from Johan planas and I do
es la na esa no del Johan planas y
n't see anyone else I don't dare to say
a no veo más nadie no me atrevo a decir
names but come on it has two
nombres pero vamos tiene dos grupos de
WhatsApp groups one is hurricane I don't know history
WhatsApp uno es huracán no sé historia
Okay
Vale
and and another group is called the rat timing
y y otro grupo se llama la rata minutaje
and it has a drawing of a rat
y tiene puesto un dibujo de de una rata
like humanized not a cartoon rat
así como humanizada no una una rata de
eh the rat timing Okay and in  These two
eh la rata minutaje Vale y en estos dos
groups are
grupos lo que están haciendo
constantly watching me, okay. And they're posting
constantemente vale Y van publicando ahí
my tweet, my clip, and the timing, I call it, I mean, it's
mi tweet mi clip minutaje lo llam o sea
like a compilation of Javi
es como una recopilación de Javi
Oliveira. I mean, how heavy is this, eh. I
oliveira O sea qué heavy es esto eh O
mean, how healthy, how healthy, of course. Now I
sea qué qué sano qué sano claro Ahora
understand that from time to time you
entiendo yo que de vez en cuando me
send me tit from Joan Plan saying, I don't know
mandéis tet del Joan plan diciendo no sé
what, Javi, I'm going to
qué Javi te voy a volver a
sue you again. Eric, a kiss, the creature
demandar Eric un beso la criatura
and of course they have a group, the rat
y claro es que tienen un grupo la rata
called me eh, the rat called me
me lo llamaba eh la rata me lo llamaba
Joan Plana on many occasions. Okay, I
Joan plana en muchas ocasiones Vale
have a whole folder where
tengo una carpeta entera donde me llama
the rat calls me, eh, sometimes mentioning me and
la rata eh algunas veces mencionándome y
other times without mentioning me, okay, for example
otras sin mencionarme vale por ejemplo
here, okay, for example here, of course, and now I
aquí vale por ejemplo aquí claro y ahora
understand that, uh, I
entiendo que
understand that everything is, eh, well,
eh entiendo que que todo es Eh bueno
[ __ ], my goodness, what a deal, what a deal, what a
pues [__] madre mía qué
deal. Well, not
movida qué movida qué movida bueno no
only did he call me Joan Plana and he
solamente me lo llamaba Joan plana y me
calls me, okay, but
lo llama vale sino que
Diego Arrabal's lawsuit,
la demanda de Diego arrabal la demanda
Diego Arrabal's lawsuit, eh, many videos, it was
de Diego arrabal eh muchos vídeos era
because he called me a rat during the entire
porque me llamaba rata durante todo el
live show, rat, sewer rat, that came
directo rata rata de cloaca que le ha
out of him, saying that it was because of a tit in
salido él diciendo que era por un tet en
which  puts a camera on her head
el que se pone una cámara en la cabeza
no no no no it wasn't for a tit in which
no no no no no era por un tet en el que
you put a camera on your head it was
te pongas una cámara a la cabeza era
because she went on several live shows several
porque se pegó varios directos varios
live shows dirty rat sewer rat I
directos rata sucia rata de cloaca yo
say Rabal that every time she mentions me she
digo rabal que cada vez que me menciona
puts everything the click compilation that
pone todo la recopilación de click que
Yoan Plana prepared
preparo yoan plana
eh of course now we see that they have these
eh claro ahora vemos que tienen estos
groups
grupos
not very healthy everything eh very healthy okay I'm going to
no muy sano todo eh muy sano vale os voy
put this okay I'm going to put this
a poner Esto vale os voy a poner esto
right now so that you can see it
ahora mismo para que para que lo veáis
Javi that you don't realize that she does
Javi que no te enteras que ella hace
research well Well she should do
investigaciones bueno Pues debería
a little research Where is her
Investigar un poco Dónde está su su
dignity and where does she find a psychiatrist
dignidad y dónde encuentra un psiquiatra
because I don't think this is very healthy
porque no creo que esto sea muy sano
okay here you have it
vale aquí lo tenéis
Okay here you have it Look at the rat
Okay aquí lo tenéis Mira la rata
footage and they put a drawing on her okay they
minutaje y le p ponen un dibujo vale le
put a doll there No in which they will
ponen ahí un muñeco No en el que ellos
laugh they will humiliate and they will do
se reirán harán humillaciones y harán
this type of things not very healthy very healthy
este tipo de cosas no muy sano muy sano
very healthy no this is the one that already had a
muy sano no esta es la que ya tuvo un
burofax she already had a burofax that Lola sent her
burofax ya tuvo un burofax que le mandó
for the issue of harassment not
Lola por el tema del del acoso no del
cyberbullying they did not send her a buras of
ciberacoso no le mandaron un buras de
Hey calm down girl this tweet is very
Oye Cálmate chica este tweet está muy
blurry I can't even see it yes I read
borroso no lo llego a ver sí que Leo
here that it is nce okay
aquí que es nce vale
clear It's that these people who
claro Es que esto que esta gente que
are denouncing the issue of the issue of
están denunciando el tema de el tema de
insults no and the right to honor and they
los insultos no y el derecho al honor y
are like very scandalized no and and they
que están como muy escandalizados no y y
celebrate the sentence for the right to
celebran la sentencia por derecho al
honor because Oh yes it's that
honor porque Oh es que sí es que
we are very outraged by this vocabulary let's
nosotros este vocabulario nos indigna
see
mucho a ver
n the movement is that you have things
n la movidad es que tú pues tienes cosas
like these
como estas
[Music]
[Música]
what is it that you were criticizing me about
qué es lo que me estabais criticando de
a video in which I was seen testifying
un vídeo en el que se me vio declarando
and everyone was laughing at that video not in
y todo el mundo se reía de ese vídeo no
which I was seen testifying in court does it sound familiar to you It
en el que se me vio declarando en el
sounds like something zoo
jugado os suena os Suena algo zoológico
says it surely starts with his [ __ ]
dice seguro empieza por su zorra
now Come here you good little [ __ ] to the
ahora Venid de buenita zorra a la a la
girlfriend of utbh I'm seeing that what is
novia de utbh estoy viendo que que es
this
esta
answer and you don't have a photo
respuesta y vos no tenéis foto despojo
so don't criticize you know that
así que no critique sabe que esta guapa
the girl is pretty and I'll give you the ass that you are
la chica y te dar del culo que lo seas
more than you [ __ ] well you know that
más que tú zorra bueno ya sabéis que
fox means cunning I've explained it
zorro significa astuto lo he explicado
a lot of times  I tried to explain it
un montón de veces lo intenté explicar
in the game and well I had to
en el jugado y bueno lo tuve que
explain it over a video in which
explicar sobre un vídeo en el que no se
that video wasn't being played Uh yes what you
estaba jugando ese vídeo Eh sí lo que se
see there in the background is sending me Lili
ve ahí de fondo sí me está mandando Lili
No, here this is another new account that has
No aquí esto es otra cuenta nueva que ha
come out very suspicious By the way, not this
salido muy sospechosa Por cierto no esta
account This, this account is not
cuenta Esta esta cuenta no es también
very suspicious either This is a new account
muy sospechosa Esta es una cuenta nueva
that they brought out now that no, that there isn't
que han sacado ahora que no que no hay
enough account about Javi Oliveira
cuenta suficiente sobre Javi oliveira
they are Well, not a suspicious account and
están Bueno una cuenta sospechosa no y
here he sends him a click of mine in which I
aquí le manda un click mío en el que yo
am blaming Tania for
le estoy echando en cara a Tania que
defending herself, okay Ah look at this ah ah Oops what a
defienda vale Ah mira este ah ah Uy qué
coincidence here Joan Planas warns
casualidad aquí Joan planas advierte a
Javi Oliveira or rather or rather or rather or rather
Javi oliveira o sea o sea o sea o sea o
or rather they pass it on
sea o sea se lo pasan primero por
WhatsApp first and then it is
WhatsApp y luego se
tweeted for a year and The damned Javi
twitea un año y El condenado de Javi
Oliveira Look By the way, they sent me in
oliveira Mira Por cierto me mandaron en
the group Lili, I don't know if you have it at
el grupo Lili no sé si lo tienes por ahí
hand, they sent me in the group that Yoan
a mano me mandaron en el grupo que yoan
Planas was responding to ik
planas estaba respondiendo a tweet de ik
Jimnez's tweet about the Dana issue and
Jiménez con el tema de la Dana y estaba
I was in Plana responding with  the issue of
yo en plana respondiendo con el tema de
the
la
sentence that is true Can you
sentencia eso es verdad Me lo puedes
look at it for me Oh what a thing Oh what a thing but
mirar Uy qué cosa Uy qué cosa pero que
if I continue that I am defaming
si sigo que dejo que yo estoy difamando
here aan plana Noa a kiss gorgeous a
aquí aan plana Noa un beso guapísima un
kiss Noa by by dec another day to Tania
beso Noa por por dec otro día a Tania
that
que
Tania defended Joan Plana who started
Tania defendía a Joan plana que se puso
celebrating the death of a girl
a celebrar un la muerte de una chica
because she was the girlfriend of a well yes that but if she
porque era novia de un pues si eso pero
has it as a
si lo tiene puesto de foto de
profile picture and made images like these and
perfil y hizo imágenes como estas y se
started saying that the girl who took her own
puso a decir que la chica que se quitó
life was
la vida era
karma or I mean what the [ __ ] are you telling me
karma o sea qué [__] me estáis contando
if that issue has already been discussed and of course
si ese tema ya se habló y claro que
Tania defended it No no it's that Tania
Tania lo defendió No no es que Tania
says and yan planas and that I have defended
dice y yan planas y que yo he defendido
a person comoan planas no no planas
a una persona comoan planas no no planas
from him He had an opinion everyone is free
de él Tuvo una opinión cada uno es libre
to express an
de expresarse una
opinion that a girl takes her own life and
opinión que una chica se quite la vida y
you say karma is an opinion because she was
tú digas karma es una opinión porque era
the girlfriend do you want to upload Tania do you want to
era la novia quieres subir Tania quieres
upload Tania do you
subir Tania
want to upload Look Tania is already in the
quieres subir Mira está Tania ya en el
chat instantly do you want to upload Tania
chat al instante quieres subir
doesn't
Tania no
answer doesn't answer No you're not going to
contesta no contesta No no vas a
answer
contestar
right you don't answer No cat
verdad no contestas No gato
smiling We just caught you Tania another
risueño Te acabamos de pillar Tania otra
multi-account I ask eh I was
multicuenta pregunto eh lo estaba
leaving it for the end but since you're
dejando para el final pero ya que estás
there We just caught you another
por ahí Te acabamos de pillar otra
multi-account or don't
multicuenta o no la llevas
you have it that's what it does taking away
tú eso es lo que hace sacar la
people's privacy what
privacidad de la gente qué
privacy do you call privacy that you have
privacidad llam privacidad a que tienes
two groups where does
dos grupos donde me
this seem healthy to me Tania does it
te parece sano esto
seem to you does this seem healthy
Tania te parece te parece sanito esto
Tania do you want to upload you're not going to answer to
Tania quieres subir no vas a contestar a
upload
subir
true no true do
verdad no verdad
you go live with someone who doesn't
te marcas un directo con una que no
respond my goodness
responde madre
yes Lili sends me the screenshot that
mía sí me manda Lili la captura de que
Joan Planas is answering nave
Joan planas le está contestando a nave
del ministerio with t of the sentence of her
del ministerio con t de la sentencia de
lawsuit mother of
la demanda suya madre del amor
beautiful love Tania town
hermoso Tania pueblo
no Tania little town no don't upload no
no Tania pueblito no no subes no
little town no Tania no Tania I'm
pueblillo no Tania no Tania a tu canal
not going to collaborate with your channel my daughter that costs
no voy a colaborar hija mía eso vale
money I'm telling you to upload here
dinero te estoy diciendo que subas aquí
I'm not going to give you something
yo no te voy a regalar a ti una cosa
because your channel has died Honestly I
porque tu canal se haya muerto De verdad
know you're all getting together now
Ya sé que os estáis juntando todos ahora
and you're trying to collaborate with each other
y estáis intentando colaborar entre
to see if you
ustedes a ver si
revive but what town or what or I continue with
revivís pero que pueblo o qué o sigo con
the live are you going to upload or  I
el directo vas a subir o
continue that you do not upload no Tania
sigo que no subes no Tania
that does not upload okay perfect family that does not
que no sube vale perfecto familia que no
upload well well Tania this is sick no
sube pues pues Tania esto es enferma no
Tania I am not going to give you anything I am not
Tania Yo no te voy a regalar nada no te
going to give you anything if you want to upload I
voy a regalar nada si quieres subir te
am telling you to upload here not to go to your
estoy diciendo que subas aquí no ir a tu
channel I am not going to give you anything my daughter you
canal no te voy a regalar nada hija mía
are nobody you have a dead channel
no eres nadie tienes un canal muerto
Random and I am not going to do it I am not going to
Random y no te voy a hacer no te voy a
give you a gift like that that is worth money
hacer un regalo como eso eso vale dinero
companies pay me for that type
las empresas a mí me pagan por ese tipo
of collaborations I am not going to give it
de colaboraciones no te la voy a regalar
to you but this is sick this is
a ti pero esto es de enferma esto es de
terrible I mean that you have two
de estar fatal O sea que tú tengas dos
groups as if you did not already have your whole
grupos como si no tuvieras ya toda tu
life on networks dedicated to the same
vida en redes dedicada a la misma
person no it is that a collaboration of
persona no tan es que una colaboración
yours is not worth money in
tuya no vale dinero de
fact it benefits you to upload here I give you
hecho te beneficia subir aquí te doy
publicity you understand me I mean Damn I'm
publicidad me entiendes o sea [__] Te
going to give you a gift of illo to your channel
voy aas un regalo de illo a tu canal
girl Yes yes it is very dead
chiquilla Sí sí está muy muerto
telesalseo Tania is dead tisimo that is why you
telesalseo Tania está muert tisimo por
have two groups dedicated
eso por eso tienes dos grupos dedicados
to
a
me this is sick
mí esto es enfermizo
Tania this is sick
Tania esto es enfermizo
Tania even writing screams no no but
Tania hasta escribiendo grita no no pero
well that is not a
bueno eso no es una
lady without  education a choni and Well
señora sin educación una choni y Bueno
but this is brutal
pero esto es brutal
eh I think you do well exposing
eh yo creo que haces bien exponiendo
harassers Of course this has to be
acosadores Claro que esto se tiene que
seen damn it's
ver [__] es
Tania Where does it say your name Well look
Tania Dónde dice tu nombre Pues mira
Tania here it says my name Look at this it's
Tania aquí dice mi nombre Mira esto es
a clip of me and your new friend moderator
un clip mío y tu nueva amiga moderadora
Javi
Javi
oliveira says the
oliveira dice la
rat What do you mean where does it say my name Tania
rata Cómo que dónde dice mi nombre Tania
this who
este quién
is it What do you mean t private WhatsApp t that
es Cómo que t WhatsApp privado t que lo
you leaked it in your live
has filtrado tú en tu directo
chav the money
poligonera el dinero
or money t finish uploading how annoying you
o dinero t termina de subir qué pesada
are it's not going to upload because she can't
eres no va a subir porque no puede
defend herself at all and this has been a
defenderse nada y esto ha sido una
catch Tania you know what I'm telling you
pillada Tania sabes que te digo que
hashtag stop
hashtag stop
harassment
acoso
#stop harassment
#stop acoso
caught fat girl you have
pillada gorda tía tenéis grupos
organized groups to send you click
organizados para mandaros click
mine the rat footage
mío la rata minutaje
we can check this link that you see
podemos comprobar este link que se ve
here it's complicated man it's
aquí es que está complicado tío es que
complicated but this link will be from
está complicado pero este link será de
any video of mine or whatever Of course
cualquier vídeo mío o de lo que sea
yes they are mentioning mentioning
Claro sí t están mencionando mencionando
one by one troop of
una a una tropa de de personas
harassed people how embarrassing you are
acosadas qué vergüenza
turboplus Oh my goodness how embarrassing you are
turboplus Oy madre mía qué vergüenza
Tania stop harassment
Tania stop acoso
tanias stop harassment Tania what you do
tanias stop acoso Tania lo que tú haces
on the internet is called
en internet se llama
harassment you only know how to insult
acoso solamente sabes insultar a la
people chase her threaten her I remind you
gente perseguirla amenazarla te recuerdo
that you threatened us that you were going to look for
que nos amenazaste con que ibas a buscar
[ __ ] and get [ __ ] out of us you know
[__] y sacar [__] de nosotros sabes
the only one you don't have a
con la única que no tienes
[ __ ] and you
[__] y
support if you know it
apoyas si lo sabes
right don't send money so she keeps
verdad no manden dinero para que siga
crying a kiss Gerardo Thank you very much
llorando un beso Gerardo Muchas
Tania stop
gracias Tania stop
harassment yes yes it's so much about you having a [ __ ] Yes it's so much about what you have a [ __ ]
acoso si si tanto va de que tienes [__]
Tania blame it on Loli who threatened you
Tania échaselo a la Loli que te amenazó
and told you
y te dijo
that she was going to tell you about your
que que te iba a contar lo de tu
husband and you
marido y te
screwed up Loli is the one who no the one of course
cagaste Loli es la que no la que claro
Loli is the one who
Loli es la que la
understood her Loli is the one who understood her
entendió Loli es la que le entendió
Of course she understood that account when she
Claro que entendió esa cuenta cuando la
made a song for Carmen because of the
le hizo una canción a Carmen por la
obsession she betrays her but this is
obsesión la delata yo pero que esto es
tremendous your mother your mother It turns me on
tremendo a tu madre a tu madre Me pone
Tania Look look look look the level they are what they
Tania Mira mira mira mira el nivel son
are family Look at what Tania just
lo que son familia Mirad lo que acaba de
posted
poner
But this What is
Tania Pero esto Qué es
Tania this Only stalkers do
Tania esto Solo lo hacen los acosadores
messing with
meterte con los
family members but my mother what have you
familiares pero mi madre que te has
done Tania why do you have to mention
hecho Tania porque tienes que mencionar
my
a mi
mother See what you are
madre Ves lo que eres
come on we've seen it all  a long
vamos ya lo hemos visto todo hace mucho
time ago what you
tiempo lo que
are Tania Come on
eres Tania Échale [__] a la
Loli Tania Come on Loli I haven't
Loli Tania Échale [__] a la Loli yo no
mentioned the father of your child I
te mencionado al padre de tu hijo te lo
mentioned him to you Loli I insinuated that he was
mencionó Loli insinuo que estuvo
detained what's more you know what you know
detenido es más sabes lo que tú sabes
perfectly well what you've been saying
perfectamente lo que has ido contando
about that
sobre ese
subject I just received a clip of Loli
tema Me acaba de llegar un clip de Loli
in which she says this is brutal man I
en el que dice es que esto es brutal tío
'm Tania the low low low low that there is
Soy Tania lo bajo bajo bajo bajo que hay
the low low that there is the rat put it
lo bajo bajo que hay lo de rata póntelo
for yourself listen to me I just received a
para ti escúchame me acaba de llegar un
click Tania in which she
click Tania en el que
says Loli just said to Tania I also
dice Loli acaba de decir a Tania también
support her financially
la apoyo económicamente
through bisom since her channel has been
a través de bisom ya que tiene el canal
demonetized Tania bowing your little head
desmonetizado Tania agachar la cabecita
and letting them threaten you is profitable
y dejar que te amenacen sale rentable
right you don't have a drop of dignity
verdad ni una gota de dignidad tienes
Tania not a drop of dignity So
Tania ni una gota de dignidad O sea que
Loli yells at you live and tells you
Loli te Grita en un directo y te dice
that if you keep crossing the line
que si te sigues pasando de la rayita
tell insinuating that they sentenced
cuenta insinuo que con condenaron a a
someone your boyfriend a partner that
alguien de a tu novio a una pareja que
you had or clearly let's go and you
tú tuviste lo ó claramente vamos y te
shut your little mouth and now there's the  Loli right
callaste la boquita y ahora está la Loli
now live the one you
ahora mismo en directo a la que tú
support so much that you like the right to
apoyas tanto que te gusta el derecho al
honor and insults and such now we are going to
honor y los insultos y tal ahora vamos a
see some rights to Loli's honor
ver una unos derechos al honor de Loli
the honor that Loli has for the
el honor que tiene Loli por la
people you swallow it because she
gente te la traga porque te
pays you you sell the things of your people Tania
paga vendes las cosas de tu gente Tania
has a price the dignity of your
tiene precio la dignidad de tu
family mother of God the euros what she
familia madre de Dios los euros lo que
does Send me the cl Lili that we are going to
hace Mándame el cl Lili que lo vamos a
put it here
poner aquí por
finally the euros what
fin los euros lo que hace
Tania does confirm it there they are going to
Tania lo confirma por ahí me van a
send me the clin they are going to send me the clin
mandar el clin me van a mandar el clin
Tania how much has she given you so that so that
Tania cuánto te ha dado para que para
you can chant like that
que para que te a chantes así la
well buy Tania
cabecita bien comprad la Tania
eh well buy Tania
eh bien comprad la Tania
eh how embarrassing Tania come on now you
eh qué vergüenza Tania vamos ya más
couldn't be more embarrassing
vergüenza no podías
taa leave us alone already go with your
dar taa dejanos en paz ya vete con tu
Marita blue leave the families in peace
Marita azul deja a las familias en paz
I advise you to leave this channel in
aconsejo que dejes este canal no vaya a
case you get fat we don't want that on
ser que engordes no queremos eso en
our
nuestras
consciences damn man but I mean they ca
conciencias [__] tío pero o sea es que
n't fall
ya no pueden caer más bajo
any lower No not even getting together between all of you
ninguno No ni juntando entre todos los
who get together Tania what are you
que os juntáis Tania que os estáis
doing  friends between people who
haciendo amigos entre gente que os
hate each other and who would never get close to each
odiáis entre sí y que no os acercaría
other in your [ __ ] life if
los unos a la otro en la [__] vida si no
it weren't for the fact that you think you're stronger against
fuera porque os creéis más fuerte contra
me by joining together
mí uniendo
okay stop making a
vale dejáis de hacer
fool of yourself if you have two groups dedicated
ridículo si tienes dos grupos dedicados
to Javi Oliveira on your
a Javi oliveira en tu
WhatsApp How the
WhatsApp Cómo
[ __ ] How the [ __ ] Don't you have
[__] Cómo [__] No tienes el
the dignity or the care that it doesn't
el la dignidad o el cuidado de que no se
leak to you Wait Wait he
filtre Espérate Espérate
went to scream
se ha ido a gritar
No WhatsApp how desperate
No whatpp qué desesperado tiene que
this guy must be to open a live stream
estar este señor para abrir un directo
with a WhatsApp screenshot he must
con una captura de WhatsApp tiene que
be on the verge of
estar a un límite de la
desperation to monetize by creating
desesperación por monetizar por crear
hate Wait Wait Wait Wait Come on, come on, you're going
odio Espérate Espérate Espérate Espérate
to cover your [ __ ] your
venga vas a tapar tus [__] tus
[ __ ] you're going to cover
[__] vas a tapar
your [ __ ] WhatsApp how desperate
tus [__] WhatsApp qué desesperado
this guy must be but this guy doesn't
tiene que estar este señor pero esta No
want the live streams to be
deea que los directos no se pueden
tapped but he didn't say that the live streams
pinchar pero no decía que los directos
can't be I just don't get it with
no se puedan Yo es que no me aclaro con
these people it's that these people have
esta gentusa es que est gentusa tiene
rules one day And the next day they don't
unas normas un día Y al otro día no las
have them but this one didn't say that
tiene pero esta no decía que no se podía
the live streams couldn't be tapped that was very
pinchar los directo que eso era
serious What is it
gravísimo
now doing the creature
Qué está haciendo ahora la criatura
or that was muted let's go to another one
u que estaba muteada vamos a una otra
that gets nervous and mutes let's
que se pone de los nervios y mutea vamos
see a little thing what are you going to see let's see
a ver una cosita qué vas a ver a ver
here here come on we have to refresh
aquí aquí venga que hay que refrescar
memories that this one really likes to put
memorias que le gusta mucho a este poner
clips he really likes to put clips and take
clips le gusta mucho poner clips y [__]
private things ehas PR Look what he's taking
cosas privadas ehas PR Mira de lo que se
advantage of Well come on let's
está aprovechando Pues venga vamos a
put let's put some eh let's
poner vamos a poner algún eh a vamos a
put let's see what he's going to put Yes yes come on come on
poner a ver qué va a poner Sí sí venga
Hello I feel obliged to make
venga Hola Me siento obligado a hacer
this video
este vídeo
to
para
concia balls she's sick per But
concia [__] ta está enferma per Pero
what are you going to put Tania
qué vas a poner Tania
a compilation of me insulting this guy well did
una recopilación mía insultando al tío
n't you say yesterday about Loli
este pues no dijiste tú ayer de la Loli
that it was okay that you insult
que estaba bien que insultas a la a la
Johana Morilla because Johana Morilla
Johana morilla porque La Johana morilla
deserved it because she had
se lo merecía porque se lo había
asked for it they are already giving her instructions
buscado ya le están dando instrucciones
no no of course I mean but really this this These are
no no claro o sea pero de verdad esto
not people who are
esto Esto no son gente que estén
well it's that we are not fighting At the same
bien es que no estamos peleando Al mismo
level
nivel
why do you put these cl of the year
para qué me pones estos cl del año
catapum if I already know what I said to all
catapum si yo ya sé lo que le dije a tod
these people and and there the things are said
esta gente y y ahí están dichas las
no  you say them so they don't get
cosas no las digáis ustedes no vay a ser
fined But what do you want, let's see, wait for your
multen Pero qué quiere a ver espera que
honor that he finds out, that he finds out what you
señoría que se entere que se entere de
do, your honor had the networks
lo que haces tu señoría las redes tenía
Mens that he finds
Mens que se entere de lo que hago de qué
out what I do about what Tania but that he finds out what I do
Tania pero que se entere de lo que hago
about what Tania is that she
de qué
is very ridiculous man it ca
Tania es que es muy ridícula tío es que
n't be true this is already
no puede ser verdad esto ya lo está
terrible look but she has people in the chat
fatal mira pero es que tiene en el chat
who tell her very well Tania very
gente que le dice muy bien Tania muy
well Tania man you have people who are
bien Tania tío tenéis a gente que está
like you Look Tania This is the
como ustedes Mira Tania Esta es la
reality I was seeing Tania I did
realidad yo estaba viendo a Tania hice
exactly the same thing but since she does
Exactamente lo mismo que pero como ella
n't have memberships, it was through the way
no tiene membresías pues fue por la vía
that you can help her
que se le puede ayudar a ella
Loli pays you
Loli te paga
Loli pays you Tania and you shut up and
Loli te paga Tania y tú te callas y
lower your
agachas las
ears because she has paid you but not to me they have to be
orejitas porque te ha pagado pero no a m
desperate I see someone
ae tienen que desesperado veo a alguien
but not you jaj
pero no a ti jaj
mimo
mimo madre
my goodness man but Loli grabbed her and
mía tío pero que la Loli la cogió y le
told her to
dijo
arrest him
que lo detengan que lo
arrest him But anyway since we're
detengan Pero bueno ya que estamos
talking about Tania who is super
hablando de Tania que está super
aware of the right to
concienciada con el derecho al
honor let's  See what she has to say
honor vamos a ver qué tiene que decir
about this, she's not going to say anything, I'll
sobre esto que no va a decir nada ya te
tell you, I
lo digo
swear, I'm super calm,
yo os lo juro estoy super tranquila un
urgent medical treatment, someone who has
tratamiento médico urgente alguien que
n't gotten anywhere in her job or in her career has
en su trabajo y en su carrera no ha
n't been able to
llegado a ningún sitio no ha podido
do anything because she's not even good enough, she's only
hacer nada porque no sirve ni para solo
good enough to go to the vouchers to watch over her
sirve para ir a los vales a vigilar a su
husband, a journalist on sale and very
marido a una periodista en oferta y muy
cheap, the sentence is going to be put in the
barata la pena se la va a meter en el
Anel and it is going to be withdrawn, eh, her
Anel y se la va a replegar eh su demanda
criminal complaint, this lady, what I'm saying is an
penal esta señora lo que dizo es una
accusation to get money because she's a creep, she's a real
cuación para sacar dinero porque es una
creep. You must
arrastrada está muy arrastrada Tú sí que
be giving her a [ __ ]
le tienes que estar dando una [__]
shame, you [ __ ]
vergüenza tuyo de
trail journalist because you
[__] periodista de rastro porque tú
're a trail peri and in s normal
eres una peri de rastro y en s normal
but I can tell you that you are a
pero le puedo decir usted que es una
journalist thrown into the mud, that you're no longer
periodista tirada al barro que ya no
good as a woman, or as a person, or
sirve ni como mujer ni como persona ni
as a human being, that you are a lady who
como humana que es usted una señora que
has stopped some treatment because
ha dejado algún tratamiento porque lo
yours is already passing, it's
suyo ya pasa lo
natural, clown, you are a clown. Be
natural payasa que es usted una payasa
careful. Although of course
de Cuidado Aunque claro igual se le
doors may have opened for you by doing what she
abrieron puertas haciendo lo que ella
says, don't [ __ ] with me, you're a [ __ ]
dice no [__] que es usted una
lady, go sell yourself and open up,
[__] señora váyase a venderse y abrirse
eh, somewhere else, you know.  perfectly go take
eh a otro lado sabe perfectamente váyase
care of her because instead of
usted a cuidarla porque aigual en vez de
taking care of her you're spreading your legs
cuidarla se está abriendo de patas por
all over the place Let's see if you get a
todos lados A ver si consigue un puesto
job to continue Because you are
de trabajo para seguir Porque usted es
a [ __ ] criminal journalist the
una [__] de delincuencia periodista la
journalist must live under the bed
periodista debe vivir debajo de la cama
while her husband goes to the bars
mientras su marido se va a los bares de
eh she must be the third discord
eh ella debe ser la tercera discordia
attic instead of asking me you wanted to
guardilla en vez de pedirme tú querías
threaten me with the money because you are a
amenazarme con el dinero porque eres una
sellout You are a [ __ ] cheap journalist and
vendía Eres una [__] periodista barata y
a [ __ ] criminal you are The worst that
una [__] delincuente eres De lo peor que
can be thrown at the vale
se puede tirar uno a la vale
Disgusting scoundrel p today Wait Wait what is he
asquerosa p hoy Espérate Espérate que me
telling me something flat not
está diciendo l una cosa plano no
flat both eyes took it this piece
plana los dos ojos lo llev este pedazo
of coward and scum you idiot eh of the
de cobarde y de Escoria t tonto eh de la
dick eh you are scum she
[__] eh tú eres una
is screaming she is totally
Escoria está gritando está totalmente
unhinged you can't even hear the video
desquiciada no se escucha ni el vídeo
she Look listen Listen
ella Mira escucha
deerc you are a fake piece of
Cucha deerc eres un falso de
[ __ ] coward and scum guy is stupid eh
[__] cobarde y deoria tío es tonto eh
of the eh you are scum what
de la eh tú eres una Escoria qué [__]
human [ __ ] you are dude not even the
humana eres tío no te quieren ni la
right wing people like you the left wing you are scum dude
gente de derecha lo de izquierda tú eres
30 madas that I already have both
una Escoria tío 30 madas queo ya los dos
eyes what I want is to
ojos lo llev yo lo que te quiero es
embarrass you in front of your audience
dejar en vergüenza delante de tu público
and for everyone to know the shitty story
y que todo el mundo Sepa la hisoria de
that you are you are a piece of [ __ ] man
[__] que eres eres Eres una [__] tío
really
de verdad
man you are a dunghill sir what
tío eres un estercolero sir para qué
character what
personaje
character if I catch you today he's
personaje si te Pillo hoy queo rápido le
going to have a heart attack quickly this is a threat Tania
va a dar algo esto es una amenaza Tania
This is something you're
Esto es algo a lo que estáis
used to from what I see
acostumbrados por lo que veo
okay I hope people start to fall
vale Espero que empiece a caer gente
criminally because these are threats
penalmente porque Estos son amenazas
okay the one who has to the one who has to
vale el que tiene que el que tiene que
pull threats because he has no
tirar de amenazas porque no tiene
arguments or way well you already
argumentos ni tiene forma pues ya se
know the type of person he is the type
sabe el tipo de persona que es el tipo
of scum that is evidently
de calaña que es evidentemente gente
uncivilized people who don't know how to
incivilizada que no sabe
debate or have two neurons connected
debatir ni tiene dos neuronas conectadas
to debate with others or dialogue
para debatir con los demás o dialogar
with others okay shameless
con los demás vale sin vergüenza
disgusting today if I catch you today there's a
asquerosa hoy si te Pillo hoy que ha un
quick trial if I catch you today too there was
juicio rápido si te Pillo hoy también
going to be a
que iba a haber un juicio
quick trial so that your husband doesn't
rápido para que tu marido no se vaya a
go to the loss of little women because you have
ir a loses de mujercitas porque t Has
lived a life a guard
vivido una vida una guard
crawling abnormal
arrastrada anormal sin
shameless thief who wants  aco for
vergüenza ladrona que quer aco por
money a false agreement for money and
dinero un acuerdo falso por dinero y no
nothing has arrived this flame here has arrived
llegó nada no ha llegado esta llama aquí
nothing has arrived he says and in my case
no ha llegado nada dice y en el caso mío
in my procedure it has
en el procedimiento mío ha
been my procedure has been
sido el procedimiento mío ha sido
declared in default because he has not
declarada en Rebeldía porque no se ha
appeared in the case, that is, he has not
personado en la causa o sea no ha
responded to the lawsuit okay
respondido a la demanda vale
and this is something that they also
e que esto es algo a lo que también
get used to eh I mean they
acostumbran eh o sea
sue them and they drag it out
e los demandan y la alargan hasta el
indefinitely or they lose in Limbo because it is
infinito o pierden en el Limbo porque se
believed that that is going to disappear from their
cree que que eso va a desaparecer de sus
lives and that in the end what is more it
vidas y eso al final lo que es más lo
prolongs it more and creates more generates more interest
alarga más y crea más genera más interés
and in the end I think that forgive me okay I do
y al final yo creo que perdonadme vale
not usually have
No suelo tener
much luck in
mucho mucha suerte en los procedimientos
judicial proceedings but it would be very
judiciales pero me resultaría muy
difficult for me if this lady were not
complicado que esta señora No la
convicted in
condenaran en
all of them Canada thief what you wanted is for a
todos canada ladrona que lo que querías
quick transfer to be made
es que se hiciera transferencia rápida
that the video is deleted eh she is
que el vídeo Está borrado eh está
calling thief is
llamando ladrona a
calling Joana Morilla a thief
está llamando ladrona a Joana morilla
because before suing her she sent her a
porque antes de demandarla le mandó una
conciliation ballot which is something that is
papeleta de conciliación que es algo que
done in court is I can
se hace en el jugado es te lo puedo
call that to you if I can call you
llamar a eso si te lo puedo llamar a ti
how important health is  uncle
qué importante es la salud tío
mentally starving Javi not even
mental muerta de hambre Javi ni siquiera
V to trial You'll see but the thing is that if he doesn't
V a juicio Ya verás pero es que si no va
go it doesn't matter Look if he doesn't go What he does is not
da igual Mira si no va Lo que hace es no
defend himself offend in court because
defenderse ofender en el juicio porque
what is he going to say the lies he says on the
qué va a decir las mentiras que dice en
internet is not that they crushed me because
internet no es que me machacaron porque
I didn't because I stopped giving him super chat the
no me porque dejé de darle super chat la
lie that the pppa invented is
mentira que se inventó la pppa la va a
she going to say it in court no that's not going to
decir ella en el jugado no eso no va a
count there what is she going to invent and in
valer allí que se va a inventar í en el
court also that he has cancer that
jugado también que tiene un cáncer que
the other day by
el otro día por
the way I think it was the one from the flight they
cierto creo que fue el del vuelo me
sent me a cli I don't know if they sent me a
mandaron un cli no sé si me mandaron un
cli or that I at so many when I was
cli o que yo a las tantas cuando estando
here working I threw a bug and
aquí trabajando le eché un [__] y lo
just saw that Jordi said host well thank goodness
justo vi que Jordi dijo [__] pues
Ja ol
menos mal que Ja ol
says without fear that he claims that this
dice sin temor que afirma que que esta
woman invented no no I have been saying it for a long
mujer se invent no no yo lo digo desde
time I mean but it can be said
hace ya tiempo o sea pero se puede decir
perfectly well eh I mean that no no let's
perfectamente eso eh o sea eso no no a
see that no more
ver que eso no se necesita ya más
study is needed eh I mean you can say that
estudio eh o sea se puede decir
calmly Eh it's not
tranquilamente eso Eh no es ninguna
defamation Not even Loli is going to sue anyone  let me
difamación Ni Loli va a demandar a nadie
say it eh be Loli has invented
que lo diga eh sea Loli se ha inventado
a
un
cancer is that I do not know who is
cáncer es que yo no sé el que est
trying to ar or defend that still at this
intentando ar o defender eso todavía
point my problem is not do you
estas alturas ya mi problema no es me
understand me or rather she must have her reasons okay
entiendes o sea sus motivos tendrá vale
But la la la doubt no does not exist it
Pero la la la la duda no no existe se
can be said calmly Loli is not going to
puede decir tranquilamente no va a
sue anyone who says that okay
demandar Loli a nadie que diga eso vale
or rather point number one we already start from
o sea punto número uno ya partimos desde
the base we start from the base in which
la base partimos de la base en la que
she is saying not only that she has
ella está contando no solamente que ha
had cancer but that she had
tenido un cáncer sino que se operó el
breast surgery and she got prosthetics at the same time that at the same
pecho y se puso prótesis a la vez que a
time that they removed the cancer
la vez que le quitaban el cáncer
okay an
vale una
invented chemo because we have not
quimio inventada porque no la hemos
seen her outside of the networks at any
visto fuera de las redes en ningún
time she has intervened in all the
momento ha intervenido en todos los
live shows okay And
directos vale Y
then audio of the sister audio of her
luego audio de la hermana audio de sus
friends or
amigos o
rather the enemies ready I am tired of
sea los enemigos listos estoy jta de
telling you XD
decírtelo XD
no no but I am not hence her bitterness
no no pero yo esto no de ahí su amargura
Oh It's your fault Tania is getting fat How and
Ay Por tu culpa Tania engorda Cómo and
Tana is still screaming in her
tana está chillando todavía en su
live show how Loli Huertas danced to her
directo có le bailaba la Loli huertas
eh let's remember how Loli Huertas danced to
eh recordemos có le bailaba a la Loli
Tania to me Loli  Huerta has not
huertas Tania a mí Loli Huerta no me ha
threatened me with getting anything from my
amenazado con sacarle nada a mi
wife As if I danced for Loli
mujer Cómo que si yo le bailaba Loli
Huerta When is it that this c is also brought
Huerta Cuándo le Es que este c también
up a lot by abnormal people the
lo sacan mucho los anormales la gente
shortest people on Twitter that can exist
más cortita de Twitter que puede existir
let's see that I danced for Loli
vamos a ver que yo le bailaba a Loli
Huerta When she gave me 300 from Super chat
Huerta Cuando me daba 300 de Super chat
of course when I didn't know her when she hadn't
claro cuando no la conocía cuando no se
invented cancer when she hadn't
había inventado un cáncer cuando no se
started defaming my friends
había puesto a difamar a mis amigos
of course and if now self-criticism appears and
claro y si aparece ahora autocrítica y
gives me 300 I dance the waca waca too
me da 300 le bailo el waca waca también
or not self-criticism just as important as
o no autocrítica igual de importante que
Mental Health is that you relate to
la Salud Mental es que te relaciones con
people who love you not your
personas que te quieran a ti no a tu
money Well or your mother's I mean this
dinero Bueno o el de tu madre o sea este
click is useless that I
click no sirve para nada que yo le
danced for a person I didn't know and she
bailaba a una persona que no conocía y
gave me super chat of course and yes and yes
me daba super chat claro y si y si me
now Isabel Fernndez also donates 300 I
dona ahora Isabel Fernández también 300
also dance for her of course how are you not going to
también le bailo claro cómo no le vas a
dance for the people who
bailar a la gente que te
collaborate with you but this but
colabora pero es que esto pero es que
this Javi la Peppa hasn't mentioned you for
esto Javi la Peppa lleva sin mencionarte
a long time and today she's going to have no
un montón y hoy no va a tener más
choice that is completely false
remedio eso es completamente falso la
Peppa Yesterday she was mentioning to me that
Peppa Ayer me estuvo mencionando que
Lily sent me the extracts okay And on the
Lily me mandó los extractos vale Y en el
day
día
[Music]
[Música]
of the day before uh we on
de en el día anterior eh nosotros el
Sunday we mentioned I don't know if it was Marina
domingo mencionamos no sé si fue Marina
or me half a second of the live we
o yo medio segundo del directo
mentioned half a second of the live we
mencionamos medio segundito del directo
mentioned that we wanted to call
mencionamos que queríamos Llamar a
Arturo requejo because he had been
Arturo requejo porque había sido
affected with Dana and we mentioned that we
afectado con la Dana y mencionamos que
wanted to invite him and that we were
lo queríamos invitar y que estábamos
contacting him Well then look what
contactando con él Bueno pues Mirad lo
the stalker did at the moment is
que hizo la acosadora al momento está
out of what it is they started
fuera de de lo que es se pusieron a
contacting Arturo and telling him how I was
contactar al Arturo y a decirle que cómo
going to get into this channel I don't know what I don't
iba a entrar en este canal no sé qué no
know how much man
sé cuánto tío
this is harassment and persecution for real I
esto es acoso y persecución de verdad O
mean uh attack against I mean if you
sea eh atentar contra o sea si tú te
find out that I'm going to bring a
enteras de que yo voy a traer aquí a una
person here to interview them and you
persona para entrevistarla y tú le
contact them to boycott that is harassment and it happens
contactas para boicotear eso es acoso y
every day and it's a
es todos los días y es un
daily Of course this lady is not going to
diario Claro que esta señora no me va a
stop mentioning me until the law stops her
dejar de mencionar hasta que la pare la
that the law is going to stop her I'm
ley que ya va a pararle a la ley ya os
telling you that the law is going to stop you
lo digo yo que va a pararle a la ley a
see of course it's going to  stop the law I have no choice
ver claro que va a parar la ley no me
but patience two years every
queda otra más paciencia dos años todos
day she has tried She doesn't know how to do it, she does
los días la ha intentado No sabe hacerlo
n't know, it was seen the other day with 80
no sabe se vio el otro día con 80
or 100 spectators which is the truth without
espectadores o 100 que es la verdad sin
jav
jav
oliveira what has happened to her has no
oliveira que lo que le ha choo no tiene
name Mental Health is
nombre la Salud Mental está
undervalued lady work it has no
infravalorada señora trabajen no tiene
name that you are not going to delete it for
nombre que eso no lo vas a borrar por
a private capture of my WhatsApp what you have
una captura Privada de WhatsApp mía lo
done Amparo that you have made fun
que has hecho Amparo que te has burlado
of all the victims of the Dana that I have made
de todas las víctimas de la Dana que yo
fun of all the victims of
me he burlado de todas las víctimas de
the Dana
la Dana
yes man I have thrown the water Me too of
si hombre he echado el agua Yo también
course Tania Tania you are shorter than
claro Tania Tania tú eres más corta que
the sleeves of a tank top
las mangas de una camiseta de
what the [ __ ] are you
tiranta qué [__] me estás
telling me that we got the wrong day we got the
contando que nos equivocamos de día nos
wrong day but stop
equivocamos de día pero dejar de
using a tragedy because you have no
utilizar una tragedia porque no tengáis
arguments stop using a
argumentos dejar de utilizar una
tragedy because you have no
tragedia porque no tengáis
arguments what are you telling me that we
argumentos qué me estás contando que nos
have side by side with all the victims of the
hemos lado de todas las víctimas de la
eh there you are not going to deceive there you are not going to
eh ahí no vas a engañar ahí no vas a
deceive look here How many punks that
engañar mira aquí Cuántos macarrilla que
you go to your mousetrap punks mousetrap
os vayáis a vuestra ratonera
come on get out of here
macarras ratonera venga fuera de aquí
long  get out of here thugs I'm glad you
largo largo de aquí macarras Me alegra
came in so I have more to block
que entréis así tengo más para bloquear
come on where is sensei You don't appear today
venga dónde está sensei No aparece hoy
sensei to block
sensei a bloquear
Tania you don't appear in yes to block Tania
Tania no apareces en se a bloquear Tania
defending a man who laughed
defendiendo a un señor que se ha reído
at a woman who is alive Thank you
de una señora que está viva Gracias
come on thank
vamos gracias a
God F you what transforms eh I
Dios F tú lo que transforma eh Ya
wish I had so many to spare to
quisiera yo tener los tan de sobra para
give them to you a kiss self-criticism Well
dártelos un beso autocrítica Bueno pues
if you give them to me one day I'll dance for you so they
si me los das algún día te bailo que lo
know she's alive by a miracle and she's
sepan está viva de milagro y se ha
been making fun of her that Amparo
estado burlando de ella que Amparo
was perfectly fine and her house was
estaba perfectamente y su casa estaba
perfectly fine the people around
perfectamente la gente del entorno de
Amparo the same day were saying that she was
Amparo el mismo día estaba diciendo que
fine that she was
se encontraba bien que está bien que ha
lost and had a scare and all that
tenido una pérdida y un susto y todo el
stuff Hey I've already apologized we've
rollo ese Oye ya me he disculpado hemos
apologized for the moment in which
pedido Perdón por el momento en el que
Amparo got involved in a controversy I
se ha metido amparo en una polémica más
can't do more I've deleted the video I've
no puedo hacer he borrado el vídeo he
apologized I offered my help more I
pedido Perdón le ofrecido mi ayuda más
can't do I can't cut my
no puedo hacer no me puedo cortar la
dick
[__]
Tania But that's not making fun of the
Tania Pero eso no es burlarse de las
victims of the one from Dana who has made
víctimas del del de la Dana que ha hecho
a fool of himself eh what he always does
el ridículo eh lo que siempre hace
trying to also throw [ __ ] at
intentar también tirar [__] a los
the rest of you are not going to cover up that [ __ ] never in your life never ever eh never Look at the ridiculousness here the the The vaciln The vaciln eh The vaciln is what they call it Oh it's true Tania this is a piece of the trial that these people have cut at their convenience in which we are
cortado a conveniencia en el que estamos
talking about a video that is not even
hablando de un vídeo que ni siquiera
part of that procedure but
forma parte de ese procedimiento pero
but anyway I repeat it to you
pero de todas maneras te lo vuelvo a
okay Well I can cut 28
repetir vale Bueno yo puedo recortar 28
and I'll see if I do it when
y Ya veré si lo hago cuando cuando sea
the sentence is final because I can
firme la sentencia porque yo puedo
cut 28 pieces in which the mother and
cortar 28 trozos en los que la madre y
the daughter lied in court saying
la hija mintieron en el juzgado diciendo
that they did not go to the press that I
que ellas no iban a la prensa que a la
surely went to the press to tell
prensa seguramente fui yo a contar las
my things that they had not given
cosas mías que ellas no habían dado
interviews in 20 that they did not talk
entrevistas en 20 que ellas no hablaban
about their life in an interview that she or rather
de su vida en interview que ella o sea
he had they brought a witness who
el tuvieron llevaron a un testigo que
lied that we are going to
mintió que lo vamos a denunciar
criminally denounce him obviously they
penalmente evidentemente
brought a witness again who
llevaron a un testigo otra vez que
lied in court they brought a
mintió en el juzgado llevaron a un
witness again who lied in
testigo otra vez que mintió en el
court that they are used to doing it
juzgado que están habituados a hacerlo
okay Of course of course I defended myself from a
vale Claro claro que me defendí de un
comment I can do it They are
comentario puedo hacerlo Me están
asking and I can do it Of course but
preguntando y puedo hacerlo Claro pero
this part of the game these two
esta parte del jugado estos dos
minutes edited to what interests
minutitos editados a lo que le interesa
Patagonia Thank you very much
patagónica Muchísimas gracias
eh I can tell you 28 I can tell you 28
eh Te puedo decir 28 te puedo decir 28
clips and 28 things in which they have
clips y 28 cosas en las que ellas han
lied not in this trial in all of them or rather
mentido no en este juicio en todos o sea
in the dog's trial they brought a witness
en el del perro llevaron a un testigo
who made a mistake even in the date in the
que se equivocó hasta de fecha en el del
dog's trial the mother has been convicted not the
perro han sido condenada la madre no la
mother as released because she is the mother but in the
madre as suelta porque es madre pero en
dog's trial Tania in which you say
el del perro Tania en el que tú dices
that you advise her not to comply with the sentence
que le aconsejas no cumplir la sentencia
Tania in the dog's trial
Tania en el del perro ha sido condenada
the daughter has been convicted the father for
la hija ha sido condenada el padre por
three quite important crimes
tres delitos bastante importantes
criminal not civil criminal okay And on top of that
penales no civiles penales vale Y encima
the witnesses are going to be persecuted for
se va a perseguir a los Testigos por
false testimony
falso testimonio
what are you putting me here of this [ __ ]
qué me estás poniendo aquí de esta [__]
Clip [ __ ] that I am
[__] de Clip que yo me estoy
justifying myself with a comment I am the
justificando de un comentario soy el
defendant do I have the right to
demandado tengo derecho a
do it in a trial I have the right
hacerlo yo en un juicio tengo derecho
even to lie being the defendant you
hasta a mentir siendo el demandado
fool that you are on edge you don't
cazurra que estáis de los nervios no
know what to get Look, he doesn't know, he doesn't
sabes qué sacar Mira no sabe no
know everything is very nice So here
sabe todo muy bonito Así que aquí
you thugs I don't want your mousetrap
macarras no quiero a vuestra ratonera
come on
venga
Here
Aquí
not here  No here I don't know AC thing no
no aquí No aquí no se AC cosa no los
balls no
[__] no los
balls Look Tania right to
[__] Mira Tania derecho al
honor calling Laura a criminal
honor llamando delincuente a Laura fa
calling her The
llamando La
Scum Salome's lawsuit hasn't
Escoria la demanda de Salomé no ha
arrived yet daughter of the great
llegado todavía hija de la gran put
whorehouse that this man uses we can't
tería que utiliza este señor no podemos
forget
olvidar
Noem we can't forget her she doesn't like to
noem no podemos olvidarla no le gusta
take out and repeat
sacar y repetir
and well we're going to repeat abuse two years
y pues vamos a repetir maltrato dos años
and at no time did he lay a hand on me
y en ningún momento me puso la mano
Oh again really with the
encima Ay otra vez de verdad con los
plana Tania Game Over Joan planas There
plana Tania Game Over Joan planas Ahí
is explained everything I say
está explicado todo lo que le digo de
back Tania Game Over Joan
vuelta Tania Game Over Joan
planas in the sentence it does not violate the
planas en la sentencia no vulnera el
honor the game over stays why
honor el game over se queda por qué
Because what I say in the game over is
Porque lo que digo en el game over es
true Tania Game Over Joan
verdad Tania Game Over Joan
plana but it is that this clip It is that this
plana pero es que este clip Es que este
clip is from a harassing riffraff from a
clip son de una gentusa acosadora de un
forum that I am insulting with all the
foro a la que estoy insultando con todo
right in the world to insult her that is why they
el derecho del mundo a insultarla por
never sue me okay this
eso no me demandan nunca vale esta
riffraff from the forum that is why no
gentusa del foro por eso no me ha
one has ever reported me okay And I am
denunciado nunca ninguna vale Y le estoy
responding with insults This clip is from
respondiendo con insulto Este cli es de
2017 2018
2017 2018
this one that we are seeing from Loli  of your
este que estamos viendo de la Loli de tu
friend the one who threatened you and you keep quiet
amiga la que te ha amenazado y te callas
is from now yesterday why does she pull a
es de ahora de ayer para qué me saca un
cl on me 6 s years ago and of course when I went to
cl hace 6 s años y claro cuando fui al
Chico Bueno school already and already when
colegio de Chico Bueno ya y ya cuando
when I was in the neighborhood with the
cuando estaba en el barrio con la
motillo I don't speak the one from C that I have
motillo no hab la de C que tengo
Tania when I was in the neighborhood with the
Tania cuando estaba en el barrio con la
motillo I won't even
motillo ya ni te
tell you another one she posted the video dude
cuento otra vez ha puesto el vídeo tío
has a problem with ler lasen she has two
tiene problema al ler lasen tiene dos
lawsuits Okay right now eh Tania leren
demandas Vale ahora mismo eh Tania leren
has two lawsuits right now one from me and
tiene ahora mismo dos demandas una mía y
another from Dallas for a series of
otra de Dallas por una serie de
disqualifying insults defamations
descalificativos insultos difamaciones
accusations of crime and Pablo is
imputaciones de delito y está Pablo
preparing another one from each of them
preparándole otra de cada uno
Tania But what the [ __ ] who the [ __ ]
Tania Pero qué [__] a quién [__] me
are you putting me here to
estás poniendo aquí para
defend yourself Yeah sure in the c that she
defenderte Sí claro en el c ese que ha
posted about the forum I call them
puesto de lo del foro yo las llamo
badfama to the forum member Okay but the thing is that
malfada a la forera Vale pero es que
Tania called Lili the other day she told her to
Tania el otro día llamó a Lili le dijo
go buy a
que se fuera a comprarse un
dildo not now in
dildo ahora no en
2019 clado only one person to
2019 clado solamente una persona a
several I get an r from a guy that I don't
varias me sale un r de un tipo que yo no
know it sounded familiar You're welcome and such that he said
no sé me sonaba De nada y tal que decía
I know a thing about Tamayo Tamayo is going to
yo s una cosa de Tamayo Tamayo me va a
make a video of me and I'm looking at that
hacer un vídeo y yo mirándome eso
thinking what the [ __ ] but you Who are
pensando qué [__] pero usted Quién es
things in life I find out about everything I find out about
cosas de la vida yo me entero de todo yo
everything I'm watching that
me entero de todo Estoy viendo eso
thinking I found out that you trust me This
pensando Se entero de que fíate tú Este
video is a compilation of Joan Plana
vídeo esta recopilación de Joan plana
dude who has been watching me all these
tío que ha estado durante todos estos
years and watching every single thing
años vigilándome y vigilando cada cosa
that they say about me eh be it Tamayo be it ler
que digan de mí eh sea Tamayo sea ler
lens be it Turbo
lens sea Turbo
plan I'm going to put I'm going to send a
plan le voy a poner Le voy a poner un
message to Tania in the chat and we
mensaje a Tania en el chat y nos
say goodbye to Tania
despedimos de Tania
okay you piece of climber and a piece of
vale pedazo de trepa y un pedazo de
pig a manual [ __ ] let's
cerdo un [__] de manual vamos a
see you son of a [ __ ] come on I'm going
ver hijo de la gran [__] venga le te voy
to pay attention to you like this in emp pij Without putting
a echado cuenta así en emp pij Sin poner
the camera on a debate Crying he left the
la cámara un debate Llorando se fue de
internet for life he came out
internet para toda la vida salió
crying from the live but Crying I
llorando del directo pero Llorando me
mean literally you can see him
refiero literalmente podéis verlo
crying No wait this not crying dude you
llorando No espera esto no llorando tío
eat my balls all of him has even
me coméis los [__] todos incluso ha
been reported to the data protection agency
sido denunciado el agencia de protección
for publishing information without
de datos por publicar información sin
third party permission but since he has been
permiso de terceros pero como ha sido
reported
denunciado
my mother I'm agreeing again he
él madre mía estoy acordando otra vez lo
threatens him with lawsuits  eh but with him he
amenaza con demandas eh pero con é lo
has it rough and now I don't know what drawers he
tiene crudo y ahora no sé qué cajones
's saying in his
está diciendo en su
live show 6 7 years ago the expert in
directo hace 6 7 años el experto en
taking out
sacar
clips that has two lawsuits the serl one
clips que tiene dos demandas la serl una
from and another from Dallas for
de y otra de Dallas por
disqualifying insults
descalificativos insultos
defamation Ah
difamaciones Ah que le viene
another one is coming, another one is coming you're talking about
otra que le viene otra estás hablando de
lawsuits I said criminal complaint eh
demandas he dicho denuncia penal eh que
you know what kind of complaint it is it's Javi
tú sabes qué tipo de denuncia es es Javi
Oliveira but you have to shut up
oliveira pero te tienes que callar
because they have you by the balls
porque te tienen pillado por los huevos
eh the one who withdrew the lawsuit
eh el que te retiró la la demanda te
has you by the balls he has you by the
tiene pillado por los huevos por los
balls eh You have to
huevos te tiene pillado eh Te tienes que
defend yourself because if not we'll go Yes very
defender todo porque si no vamos Sí muy
sick very sick I am very sick yes we are
enferma muy enferma estoy muy enferma sí
all
todos estamos
sick no we are not healthy we are
enfos no no estamos sanita estamos
healthy he is very healthy I am happy for
sanita él está muy sano me aleg de
now he allows him to say barbarities
momento le permite decir barbaridades
harassing the entire internet like
acosando a todo internet como que no se
nobody forgets that this man falsely accused me
olvide nadie que este señor me acusó
in front of I don't know how many people he
falsamente delante de no sé cuánta gente
sent he sent his community to
mandó mandó a su comunidad que me
harass me that I had taken his
acosara con que yo le había quitado el
bread eh with the unet thing that I had
pan eh con lo de la unet que yo le había
taken his bread eh
quitado el pan eh
the message doesn't come out sailor eh  t la
no sale el mensaje marinera eh t la
marinera my message is not coming out
marinera no sale mi mensaje porque
because they have me blocked so I can't
porque me tienen bloqueado para que no
comment but nothing Tania Well it will get to
pueda comentar pero nada Tania Bueno ya
you okay I have tried to put it
te llegará vale Te lo he intentado poner
in the chat but it is not reaching you because you
en el chat pero no te llega porque me
have me banned but Tania what what nothing that
tienes baneado pero Tania que que nada
Loli you
que Loli
that Loli threatened you okay You shut your
te que Loli te amenazó vale Te callaste
mouth because you are scared and what and what you
la boca porque te acojonas y que y que
put a price on the defense of your
le pusiste precio a la defensa a tu
family because of course this lady
familia porque claro esta señora te
threatened you with taking out I don't know what that they had
amenazó con sacar no se qu de que habían
arrested your partner and not only did
detenido a tu a tu pareja y no solamente
you keep quiet but now you are
te callaste sino que ahora estás
receiving her
recibiendo su
money so well you have put it you have
dinero entonces pues le has puesto te
sold out you have sold out yours you have
has vendido has vendido a los tuyos te
sold out for the disgusting visas
has vendido por por los visum asquerosos
of
de la de la
Loli there is nothing that made me more
Loli que no hay nada que me diera más
ashamed than that well anyway let's get back to the
vergüenza que eso bueno total volvemos a
subject Loli okay Let her
lo del tema Loli vale Ya dejarla que
scream if you tell me something important
grite si algo importante me lo decís
okay But well she is going to be there hitting river come on let's go
vale Pero bueno va a est ahí pegando río
back to Loli because this one
vamos vamos a volver a a Loli que esta
really fails her honor very bitter life
sí que falla al honor vida muy amargada
your husband will have to be with
tu marido con razón tendrá que estar con
little women in bars with good reason and you
mujercitas en los bares Y con razón
will have to drag it  of the
tendrás que ir arrastrando lo de los
elderly wretch You are a [ __ ]
ancianos desgraciada Eres una [__]
wretch abnormal lady disgrace of a
desgraciada señora anormal desgracia de
human person Scum garbage aunt eh you
persona humana Escoria basura tía eh tú
are sick very sick this lady is
estás malita muy malita esta señora es
a sick person this lady is a
una persona enferma esta señora es una
lady that if you throw it in her face she
señora que si te la tiras a la cara no
has no balls to say that this lady is
tiene balios de decir eso esta señora es
a very vile lady this lady is
una señora muy rastrera esta señora es
a lady without humanity this lady is
una señora sin humanidad esta señora es
a lady that sells out for the cheapest that must have been on
una señora vendida de lo más barato que
all the
que habrá pasado por todos las series de
television series and everything to see if they would give her
televisión y todo para ver si le daban
a position and she has realized that she is only
un puesto y se ha dado cuenta que solo
good for opening her leg eh And that she
sirve para abrir la pata eh Y que se
has to hide under the bed
tiene que esconder debajo la cama
while her husband is out at bars in
mientras su marido está en los bares en
bars of ladies okay lady that's what that
bares de señorit vale señora eso lo que
Will be her husband come crying because there is
ese Será su marido venga llorando porque
a deceased and I curse all the
hay un fallecido y me cago en todos los
dead that Christ gave birth to eh you are worse
muertos que parió Cristo eh eres peor
than a mortal disease you are something very
que una enfermedad mortal eres algo muy
extremely disgusting
sumamente asqueroso
because they are criminal people
porque son gente delincuente gente
sick people without treatment
enferma gente sin tratamiento
criminals aggressive criminals
delincuentes delincuentes agresivos
abusers
maltratadores
eh psychological abusers he is going to lie down and
eh maltratadores psicológicos el se a
knock him down there and if he doesn't have
tumbarse a tumbar por ahí y si no tiene
anyone to knock him down because he likes the
quien la tumbe porque le gusta más las
ladies in the bars better, go eat a
señoritas de los bares vaya se comre un
comforter but leave my life alone this
consolador pero deje mi vida en paz esta
lady is from this lady should be
señora es de esta señora debería estar
arrested and behind bars And this one should have
detenida y entre rejas Y a esta si que
the key thrown into the sea so she
habría que tirarle la llave al mar para
couldn't get out this is a
que no pudiera salir esto es un hecho
poisonous fact this is worse than a
venenoso esto es peor que una enfermedad
deadly disease too Fat fat has stopped the
mortal too Gordo gordo ha dejado el
treatment and is a tumb fring the day she
tratamiento y es una tumb fring el día
goes through life period she is a
que va por la vida punto es una tía
frustrated woman because her husband is in the
frustrada porque su marido está en los
bars of little women and because eh she has
bares de mujercitas y porque eh se ha
swallowed everything from the old people who were
tragado todo lo de los ancianos que
around her it is since she has
tuviera a su alrededor es ya que ha
appeared on tv she is famous it should be
salido en la tele es famosa habría que
published that Joana
hacer que se publicara que Joana
morillas is so creepy and disgusting she is
morillas es así de rastrera y asquerosa
a degenerate she has an
es una degenerada a tiene una
atrocious family degeneration she has a
degeneración de familia atroz tiene una
creepy and disgusting family she has a
familia rastrera y asquerosa tiene una
crappy life and you want to bring it down
porquería de vida y me lo quieres aacar
on me I hope he sees her that I am going to show you
a mí Ojalá que la vea que voy a enseñar
the papers but the
Yo los papeles pero los papeles del
truck papers they are going to
camión le van a
report you
denunciar
grave run and report now run come on
tumba corre y Denuncia ya corre venga
with the four hairs of your [ __ ] you
con los cuatro pelos del [__] te vas
run away Look at the other day when
corriendo Fíjate que el otro día cuando
we were wrong because the truth is we were
nos equivocamos porque la verdad nos
wrong it was a  very
equivocamos fue un momento muy
unfortunate moment Okay We apologize and the
desafortunado Vale Nos disculpamos y el
subject Well it's over okay but They opened I
tema Pues ya pasó vale pero Se abrieron
don't know how many live streams I don't know how many
no sé cuántos directos no sé cuántos
tweet spaces on Twitter no empathy
tweet space de Twitter no la empatía
okay empathy empathy not a single [ __ ]
vale la empatía la empatía ni un [__]
live stream was opened the next day on
directo se abrió al día siguiente sobre
this subject as far as I know eh as far as I know eh
este tema que yo sepa eh que yo sepa eh
Not
Ni
one to me this seems more
uno a mí esto me parece más
serious
grave más
stronger not
fuerte ni
one why What does it
uno por qué
matter what or
Qué importa el qué o el
who Not one
quién Ni uno
saurian not a live stream of indignation not
saurio ni un directo de indignación ni
a
un
space in fact most were in the
space de hecho la mayoría estaban por el
chat eh to the one from Troy
chat eh al de Troya
Look Tania was there cheering her on
Mira la Tania estaba por ahí animándola
And by the
Y por
way speaking of the spaces this witch that
cierto hablando de los space la bruja
evil bug still starts to this day to be a
malo se pone a a día de hoy todavía a
pain in the ass with empathy great
dar por culo con la empatía gran
quality empathy what a shame the one who does
cualidad la empatía qué desgracia el que
n't have it Pilar have you had
no la tiene Pilar usted ha tenido
empathy with the victims of cancer
empatía con las víctimas del cáncer
when Lolly invented it or
cuando Lolly se lo inventó o
when Peppa with whom you
cuando Peppa con la que
collaborate raised money and forgot to
colaboras recaudó dinero y se le olvidó
give it empathy you have no shame nor do you
darlo empatía no tenéis vergüenza ni ni
really know her I mean you have no
la conocéis de verdad O sea no tenéis
shame nor the
vergüenza ni la
s this lady is for real no she puts
s esta señora es de verdad no ella pone
a drawing here I  I imagine this is
aquí un dibujo yo me imagino que esto es
a drawing made with an
un dibujo hecho con una Inteligencia
artificial intelligence of those that make drawings
artificial de estas que te hacen dibujos
of your photos and puts a drawing so as not to
de tu fotos y pone un dibujo para no
put her obviously
ponerse a ella evidentemente
eh but I see it as normal with the role she
eh pero lo veo normal con con el papel
has
que tiene
on the internet I see it as normal that she doesn't Put
en en internet veo normal que no Ponga
her face so that it is not her Of course what she
su cara para que no se le Claro que lo
does is a [ __ ] shame what
que hace una puñetera vergüenza qué
quality empathy is you are
cualidad la empatía está estás
using a tragedy to try to
utilizando una tragedia para intentar
beat the people you
batir a la gente a la que
hate you are using a tragedy If you
odias estás utilizando una tragedia Si
had empathy today you open another space of
tuvieras empatía abres hoy otro space de
toxic characters for
personajes tóxicos para la
Loli you open another space for
Loli abres otro space para la
Loli obviously of course Tania tries to
Loli evidentemente claro Tania intenta
justify every man so Although
justificar todo hombre tan Aunque la
I saw her give us a direct sub here
viese darnos sub directo ha aquí
cutting us I would say that Of course it's that we
cortarnos diría que Claro que es que nos
have thrown ourselves to the knife which is
hemos tirado nosotros al cuchillo que es
something we are a little exaggerated but
algo somos un un poquito exagerados pero
if she is denying that she even threatened to
si está negando que incluso amenazara
hit Joana that she
con pegar a con pegar a a Joana que la
told her that she was going to grab her by the hair and
dijo que le iba a [__] de los pelos y
drag her and put her through the I
la iba a arrastrar y la iba a meter por
don't know what of her mother and she is
el no sé qué de su madre y lo está
denying it that she is there she doesn't even understand
negando que está allí no se entera ni de
what she is seeing Well yes she
lo que está viendo Bueno sí que se
understands they are telling me that she continues eh
entera me están diciendo que sigue eh
you are
tú eres
worse you are
peor tú eres
worse So if you have what it takes get
peor Así que si tienes lo que hay que
up here Francisco Javier
tener subes aquí Francisco Javier
Oliveira I don't have the channel monetized I don't give a
oliveira no tengo el canal monetizado me
[ __ ] get up here we
importa tres [__] subes aquí lo
talk about it because I'm not going to give you
hablamos porque no te pienso regalar
60,000 views I
60.000 visualizaciones eso te lo
assure you you get up here with your pair of balls
aseguro subes aquí con tu par de huevos
with those balls with that one of balls with
con es huevos con ese de huevos con
beating Ricky's face edit eh You get
partirle la cara al Ricky edit eh Te
up here and we talk about what we have I can
subes aquí y hablamos lo que tenemos yo
see all my stuff
se ven todas mis cosas
man there's no mod and I'm up for everything and
tío es que no hay mod y estoy a todo y a
nothing no no but it's that they see all all all all
nada no no pero es que se ven todas
my stuff man everything everything everything they
todas todas todas mis cosas tío todo
know all my controversies they
todo todo se saben todas mis polémicas
see everything they enjoy my content a lot
lo ven todo disfrutan muchísimo de mi
and there he is with his
contenido y ahí está él con su vídeo de
loop video of his boss I don't know what else I'm telling you
bucle de su jefe no sé que otra cosa que
Look they're putting up videos of
os digo Mira están poniendo vídeos de
what her boss does to her it's that
que su jefe le le pone es que otra cosa
the girl can't do anything else But she has to
no puede la chiquilla Pero tiene que
deny it of course to hide everything it's
negarlo claro para disimular todo está
justified that she started counting
justificado que se ha puesto a contar
the times they talk let's count
las veces que hablan vamos a contar
later the fish that She talks about Javier
luego la peces que habla Ella de Javier
Oliveira Although the title is that if SAP
oliveira Aunque el título sea que si SAP
has broken a nail let's see the fish
se ha roto una uña vamos a ver la peces
that She talks about Javier Oliveira  in their
que habla Ella de Javier oliveira en sus
live shows So that harassment would have the
directos Entonces eso acoso tendría
right Javi to [ __ ] on his entire
derecho Javi a cagarse en toda su
generation no and say that he's going to
generación no y y decir que la va a
grab her and punch her twice in
[__] y le va a meter dos puñetazos en
the nose or how would he have the right I suppose
la nariz o cómo tendría derecho Supongo
Because if she thinks Loli has the
Porque si ella cree que Loli tiene
right to say the nonsense she
derecho a decir la barbaridad de que
says because she's mentioned I don't know where
dice porque se la nombra no sé dónde que
what does it have to do with Johana telling about the
qué teng que ver Johana cuenta lo del
sensei sitting I don't know what
sensei sentado no sé qué es lo que ha
happened with the sensei sitting let's see s that It
pasado con lo del sensei sentado a ver s
's obvious that they fought and they do
que Es evidente que se han peleado y ya
n't talk to each other anymore okay I imagine that Juan
no se hablan vale Yo me imagino que Juan
in order not to lose her he will have her because she's the the
para no perderla la tendrá porque es la
only one he has there that
la la única que tiene ahí que que que
is capable of sacrificing herself for putting
sea capaz de sacrificarse por por poner
his nonsense and for giving attention to his
sus tonterías y por darle bola a sus
nonsense you understand Because
tonterías me entiendes Porque todo el
everyone on the internet knows what happened knows
mundo en internet sabe lo que pasó sabe
how she behaved knows why things happened
cómo se portó sabe por qué pasaron las
no And the only one so so so stupid
no Y la única tonta tan tan tan tonta
as to give attention and to follow the r
como para darle bola y para seguir el r
r is Tania or rather even legun pasa
r es la Tania o sea hasta legun pasa lo
uploaded it one day because it's a channel also
subió un día porque es un canal también
dedicated to me and uploaded it one day because it
dedicado a mí y lo subi un día porque
was against jav oliveira  but once he
era contra jav oliveira pero una vez que
uploaded it he also had because he didn't agree with him
lo subió también tuvo porque no le daba
on everything and with Joan he will also
la razón en todo y con Joan también se
fight you know Look I already said this at the
peleará sabes Mira esto ya lo dije yo en
time and I remember that also She said
su día y me acuerdo que además Ella dijo
like haha haha I'm never going to fight
como que jaja jaja yo no me voy a pelear
with my sensei has fought of course
nunca con mi sensei se ha peleado claro
and sense and Joan for sure let's do this I without
e sense y Joan seguro vamos esto yo sin
without seeing a conversation I'm telling you
sin ver una conversación ya te lo digo
in private laugh at her she's stupid she's
en privado rien de ella es tonta es
fat she's illiterate she can't write she can't read she can't
gorda es analfabeta no sabe escribir no
speak You know she smokes that's
sabe leer no sabe hablar Sabes fuma es
everything he's the complete prototype of the
todo el es el prototipo completo de
person they would mess with And
persona con el que ellos se meterían Y
surely in private they're making fun
seguramente en privado se estén burlando
of her and they're using her and all that
de ella y la están utilizando y todo el
stuff, I mean and anyone who knows
rollo ese o sea y cualquiera que conozca
the story knows it look at the gameover
la historia lo sabe miraros el gameover
and there you will say Tania is the
y ahí diréis la Tania es el perfil
perfect profile what happens is that they don't have
perfecto lo que pasa es que no tienen
another person who is going to
otra persona que que se vaya a
sacrifice herself to defend him at
sacrificar para defenderle a él ya a
this point I mean
estas alturas
things happened for a reason it happens
o sea las cosas pasaron por algo pasa
that she wasn't there but since she's an
que ella no estaba ahí pero como es
idiot she talks as if she were you
idiota pues habla como si estuviera
know because if Johana names her once
sabes porque si Johana la nombra una vez
what does Johana have to do with that in that
qué tendrá que ver Johana en ese en esa
thing but no  everything is justified yes
vaina pero no todo está justificado si
everything is justified here a man
aquí todo está justificado un hombre
vent his sorrow that he doesn't vent
desahógate la pena que no se desahoga
with you and your whole family of course the
contigo y con toda tu familia claro la
sorrow that he doesn't vent with your whole
pena que no se desahoga con toda tu
family is shameless it's
familia es una desvergüenza es una
crazy what's happening here is
locura lo que está pasando aquí es que
crazy it's a group that look like these
es de locura es un grupo que parecen los
bullies from the institute who have
bullis estos del instituto que se han
believed they have the right to everything the slightest thing
creído con derecho a todo a la mínima
that steps on them they go to the director but they
que les pisa van al director pero ellos
are crushing everyone here they
están machacando aquí a todo el mundo
are the majority let's say by themselves they
son mayoría vamos dicho por ellos mismos
are the majority but what are we supposed to
son mayoría pero que se supone que lo
do to them The minority is something very
que le hacemos La minoría es algo muy
serious It's something very serious But they are
grave Es algo gravísimo Pero ellos son
five or six channels giving trayas
cinco o seis canales dando trayas sin
nonstop they don't have the majority any other
parar no tienen la mayoría ningún otro
content than crushing crushing
contenido que no sea machacar machacar
crushing no No look Marin is talking to me what does it have to
machacar no No mira me está hablando
do with someone smoking
Marin que tiene que ver que alguien fume
so that they laugh at her Joan Planas
para que se rían de ella Joan planas a
tells people who smoke that they are
la gente que fuma le dice que son
drug addicts and it has been said to Tania in her
drogadictos y se ha dicho a Tania en su
face eh I have here the click where she
cara eh yo tengo aquí el click donde se
says it in her face and Tania says yes
lo dice en su cara y Tania dice sí
guana talk about other channels almost all of
guana hablar de otros canales casi todos
them some Talk  over there a
ellos alguno Habla por ahí de salseo un
little gossip to cover up but come on the
poco mete para disimular pero venga los
next two important hours are
siguientes las dos horas importantes son
youtubers and it's to crush insult mess
youtubers y es machacar insultar meterse
with the family to suck on Loli that they
con la familia a chuchar a Loli que la
have her like the guard dog La
tienen como el perrito de presa La
Chucho I say something emphatically Oh what
Chucho le digo algo hincapié Ay lo que
they said on such channel Uy I think it was
han dicho en tal canal Uy yo creo que
for Loli I think it was for Loli
iba por Loli yo creo que iba por Loli
that for Loli is like lighting a
que eso para Loli es como encenderle una
match to her side that for Loli is
cerilla al lado eso para Loli es
lighting the fuse Uy what they said
encenderle la Mecha Uy lo que han dicho
I think it was for Loli the
yo creo que iba para Loli ya está
job is done here comes Loli that's the one who
trabajo hecho ya va Loli que es la que
immolates herself here comes Loli with a knife for whoever
se inmola ya va Loli a cuchillo a por el
first that channel says that
que primero que ese canal diga que tal
then here comes Loli with a knife and they will still
pues ya va Loli a cuchillo y todavía
sleep at night and they will be very
dormirán por la noche y estarán muy a
comfortable But they are very good channels eh of
gusto Pero son canales muy buenos eh de
very good people man Sure sure sure
muy buenas personas hombre Claro claro
some even defend
claro algunos incluso vamos defienden
movements and everything eh Yes yes yes yes
movimientos y todo eh Sí sí sí sí
some defend movements and everything
algunos defienden movimientos y todo
good it's pathetic let's see some
bueno es patético vamos a ver algunas
things it's that it's let's
cosillas es que es de
see that Ah everyone and that being all there
a ver que Ah todos y que estar todos ahí
like a tick sucking its blood
como una garrapata chupando su sangre
you have shame no  Are you ashamed
tenéis vergüenza no tenéis vergüenza
Tania, they should threaten you,
Tania te tendrían que amenazar a ti
share your teeth, let's see how it goes, let's
compartirte los dientes a ver qué tal a
see how it goes with the [ __ ] and how crybaby you
ver qué tal con la cusica y lo Llorona
are, let's see how it goes, she was still denying, let's
que eres a ver qué tal que todavía
see, she
estaba negando vamos a verlo todavía
was still denying that the lady
estaba negando que la señora ha
threatened Joana Morilla He
amenazado a Joana morilla Es que la ha
threatened to hit her, he messed with
amenazado con pegarle se ha metido con
her deceased mother, with her father with everything,
su madre fallecida con su padre con todo
with her profession as a woman, he
con su profesión como mujer le ha
called her the four letters and every
llamado las cuatro letra y de todo
man, that's enough, man, that's enough,
hombre ya está bien hombre ya está bien
even for you who don't have any
incluso para vosotros que no tenéis ni
[ __ ] shame it's excessive, that's enough, that's enough, so
puñetera vergüenza es excesivo ya está
much cloth, that's enough and then
bien much tela ya está bien y que luego
you go about what you want, that you love her, you
vayáis de que queréis de que la queréis
appreciate her, the only thing you want is that she's
la apreciáis lo único que queréis so Es
a gang of cowards, don't you don't want to
Una Pandilla de cobarde no la no queréis
turn against her because if not, that's what
poner en contra porque si no lo que os
you are and that's what you are to begin with. In
es a vosotros y sois eso para empezar O
other words, Tania has sold eh her defense to
sea la Tania ha vendido eh su defensa a
her family, I mean, because look at Tania, I'm
su familia o sea porque mira la Tania os
going to tell you one thing and I'm going to put my
voy a decir una cosa y me voy poniendo
boots on because right now it's time to
los botines que ya mismo es la hora de
train, okay, look at you  do you remember what
entrenar vale mira os acordáis la que la
Tania did to FJ do you remember what
Tania le lió a FJ os acordáis la que la
Tania did to FJ
Tania le lió a FJ
because in another WhatsApp a photo
porque en otro wasa se filtró una foto
of her son or something like that was leaked and FJ
del hijo o algo por el estilo que FJ lo
deleted it and she caused such a mess do
borró y liola tan un pollo de la [__]
you remember No, Tania with
[__] os acordáis No pues Tania con con
Lolly she didn't have the guts to cause the same
Lolly no ha tenido [__] de liar el mismo
mess or half of that mess for
pollo o la mitad del de ese pollo por
threatening to expose that her husband according to
amenazarla con sacar que su marido según
Loli They have
Loli lo Han
arrested them, they are
detenido
[ __ ] cowards so you already proved it that you
unos [__] cobardes tan tú ya lo
[ __ ] yourself from the legs
demostraste que te cagaste por las patas
down you already proved it and then the
para abajo ya lo demostraste y luego lo
only thing you want is for it to be as worst as
único que queréis es que quede lo peor
possible and for the others to adjust even
que pueda quedar y que ajuste los demás
still He says that at the end of the
yasta todavía Dice t que al final del
live he will remember the
directo recuo el
live but but it's that you have no
directo pero pero es que tú no tienes
shame or the acquaintance well no I can
vergüenza ni la conocido bueno no que ya
see you now I can see you but what can you say that
te veo ya te veo pero que puedes decir
this is remembered that that
que se recuo esto eso que hizo esa
lady did you can say that there was a
señora tú puedes decir que eso había
way to get it back on track not even by putting music on Not even
manera de reconducir ni poniendo música
if they put the east of the Vatican
Ni aunque pongan el este del Vaticano
there and still cloths with name at the end
ahí y todavía pañitos c nombre al final
Rec hosted the live  because I put on
Rec condujo el directo porque puso
music you want to go [ __ ] yourself
música te quieres ir a tomar por por ahí
where losin So right now I
por donde losin O sea que yo ahora mismo
can tell you here that I'm going to kick your
te puedo decir aquí que te voy a partir
teeth in and if later at the end I put on
los dientes y si luego al final pongo
a song laughing at you man then I
una canción riéndome de ti hombre pues
've already redirected the live show we're not going to
ya he reconducido el directo no vamos a
all copy that formula give it a go
copiar todos esa fórmula a darle cañ tñ
call her everything threaten her and then we
a llamarla de todo amenazarla y luego
put on a ridiculous song but we
ponemos una canción ridiculiza pero
say that we have redirected the
decimos que hemos reconducido el
live show It's that you really are you are I am the
directo Es que de verdad sois sois soy
worst Look Tania since you're
de lo peor Mira Tania desde que estás
here YouTube is a little bit worse since
aquí YouTube es un poquito peor desde
you've been here Tania that's what I'm
que estás tú por aquí Tania así te lo
telling you since you've been here you haven't
digo desde que estás tú por aquí ni has
contributed anything to the gossip because you haven't
aportado nada al salseo porque no has
known how to do it and you've thrown it all away
sabido hacerlo y lo has tirado todo a
and the only thing you've
tomar por culo y lo único que has
contributed is bad vibes and grime and disgust that
aportado es mal rollo e grima y y asco
's the only thing you've contributed here to
es lo único que has aportado tú aquí a
this whole world of YouTube since
todo este mundo de YouTube desde que
you've been here because you have contributed absolutely nothing to the world of
estás tú por aquí porque al mundo del
gossip nothing
salseo no has aportado absolutamente
[ __ ] the only one who has
nada nada [__] el único que has
contributed Thank you so much Rosaca
aportado Muchísimas gracias rosaca
thank you very much beautiful
muchas gracias guapa
people and [ __ ] the only one who has brought it
gentos y [__] el único que ha portado
turns out that he was going  let's see about gossip and
resulta que iba a ver de salseo y de
gossip that according to her she liked
salseo que según ella que le gustaba el
gossip and everyone this from the heart
salseo y todo el mundo este del corazón
and everything let's see send me here a click
y todo a ver me mandan por aquí un click
Carmen says predicting the future with
Dice Carmen prediciendo el futuro con
Tania youtuber there is a new youtuber
Tania youtuber hay una nueva youtuber
who is a friend of ave nocturna who is a she is a
que es amiga de ave nocturna que es
gem she is a gem this
un es una joyita es una joyita esta
new youtuber this is going to she is going to
nueva youtuber esta le va a dar le va a
give she is going to give
dar el follón a le va a dar al follón a
Oliveira a hard time her name is Tania I think
oliveira se llama Tania creo que está
she is also doing that they are doing
haciendo también ella que están haciendo
live shows everyone before I was there
directos todo el mundo antes estaba yo
In the mornings now Everyone wants the
Por las mañanas ya Todos quieren las
mornings her name is Tania and she is a new
mañanas se llama Tania y es una nueva
youtuber from the part of ave nocturna
youtuber de la parte de de ave nocturna
who is a spectacle if you want I
que es un espectáculo si queréis lo
will put it a little to Tania because you have to
pongo un poco a Tania porque es que hay
see Tania Tania is going to give
que ver a Tania Tania le va a dar el
Oliveira a hard time she has few
follón a oliveira tiene pocos
subscribers but she is from the part of ave
suscriptores pero es de la parte de ave
nocturna but Tania goes Tania is going to give
nocturna pero Tania va Tania va dar
[ __ ]
follo ya
you will see she has not carried absolutely anything
veréis no ha portado absolutamente nada
Hey what is Tania doing right now I ca
Oye qué está haciendo la Tania ahora
n't believe it she doesn't have the balls
mismo no lo puedo creer no tiene huevos
to upload to me  channel eh To the one who didn't
a subir a mi canal eh A la que no ha
want to upload and is watching is
querido subir y está viéndose está
watching the debate she had with me
viéndose el debate que tuvo conmigo hace
a year or
un año o
two ago very healthy behavior eham
dos un comportamiento muy sanito eham
very healthy eh family instead of having
muy sanito eh familia en vez de haber
uploaded she starts watching the debate why does
subido se pone a ver el debate para qué
n't she have a word the one who has zero
no tiene palabra la que tiene cero
credibility according to him has no balls and
credibilidad según él no tiene huevos y
goes to town That's jabi oliveira eh
se va al pueblo Ese es jabi oliveira eh
That's the titan of javio oliveira yes eh
Ese es el titán de javio oliveira sí
Yes Francisco oliveira cuts the
eh Sí Francisco oliveira corta el
live and uploads come on run come here I'll
directo y sube anda corre que vengas que
wait for you Fran Javier cuts the live
te espero Fran Javier corta el directo
that you're doing and uploads here uploads here
que estás haciendo y sube aquí sube aquí
king of the fake
rey del fals
channel that you weren't anyone and starts
canal que que no eras ningú y se pone a
reacting to the debate he had with me
reaccionar al debate que tuvo conmigo
two years ago I can't I can't
hace dos años yo no puedo yo no puedo
ported the channel to hell and the
porado el canal a tomar por saco y lo
only thing it has contributed has been bad vibes
único que ha aportado ha sido mal rollo
enmity the channel has thrown it up the
enemistad el canal la ha tirado a tomar
ass Yes, I mean the channel no longer has
por culo Sí o sea el canal ya no tiene
monetization because it doesn't comply with the rules they have taken
monetización porque no cumple las normas
away the monetization from the Channel
le han quitado la monetización al Canal
and the channel throws it up the ass nothing
y el canal la tira a tomar por culo nada
more than it has it for this from time to
más que lo tiene para esto de vez en
time it opens it and starts watching there  She's really into
cuando lo abre y se pone a ver ahí
trouble,
está metida donde hay un fregado allá
even she doesn't get lost in the chat, one does
hasta ella en el chat no se pierde uno
n't sleep 24 hours a day, she doesn't sleep
no duerme 24 horas al día que no duerme
because it doesn't matter when it is, whether it's
porque es que da igual cuando sea si es
in the morning, at night, in the afternoon,
por la mañana si es por la noche si es
if it's 24 hours a day, she's
por la tarde si es las 24 horas del día
on guard, she sleeps on the couch
está está de guardia duerme en el sofá
with one eye open just in case there's
así con un ojo abierto por si acaso hay
a channel where
un canal donde se esté injuriando a
someone is being insulted And
alguien Y
hammering away, wait Lili, check it out for me, so
machacando espérate Lili compruébamelo
she can get into it, get into the
para salir ella en el meterse ella en el
chat to write, that's her, of
chat para escribir Esa es ella Desde
course, you must have a lot of free time.
luego que debes tener mucho tiempo libre
Of course, no. You must have nothing
Claro que sí No Debes tener ninguna cosa
to do or anything to be
que hacer ni nada de nada para estar
having so much free time for everything
tener tanto tiempo libre para todo lo
you have, 24 hours a day, no matter where the
tienes 24 horas da igual donde sea el
mess is. There she is, stuck in the chat, one of each other, the
jaleo Ahí está ella metida en el chat de
other, the other, those who
uno de otro del otro del otro de los que
are from another party, those who are from
son de otra cuerda de los que son de la
hers, those who are from, it doesn't matter. There
suya de los que son de da lo mismo Ahí
she is, a spirit around here,
ella un espíritu por aquí rondando
latent, 24 hours a
latente 24 horas al
day, going, going very per, eh, going, going very
día va va muy per eh va va muy
harmed, grabbing
perjudicada agarrar de los pelos a a
Johan Moriches by the hair, it's just  no I'm not
Johan moriches justo es que no no me
mistaken let's see let's see let's see
equivoco es que a veré a ver a ver a ver
the brand yes
la marcasi
this afternoon I wrote it in x I
esta tarde mismo lo he escrito en x he
wrote to me it's that I'm scared this
escrito a mí es que me da miedo esta
woman finds you on the street and
mujer te la encuentra por la calle y te
pulls you grabs you by the hair and she just
arranca te agarra de los pelos y justo
threatened to grab
acaba de amenazar con agarrar de los
Joana Morillas by the hair this is a lie
pelos a a Joana morillas esto es mentira
what the brand wasi just said is a
lo que acaba de decir la marca wasi es
lie I was there both of them live eh
mentira yo estuve los dos directos eh
eh practically in radio mode
eh en modo radio prácticamente
and at no time did I hear
y en ningún momento yo escuché
correct me if I'm wrong please eh I
corregirme si me equivoco por favor eh
came out here
he salido aquí
the content creator collected by
el creador de contenido recogido por
Javi Oliveira watch out
Javi oliveira ojo
eh the mother who gave birth to me but I didn't
eh la madre que me parió pero yo no
hear that Loli Huertas was going to
escuché que Loli huertas la iba a
drag her by the hair Tania didn't hear that
rastrar de los pelos eso no lo escuchó
this is a lie that's a lie I didn't hear it this is a
Tania esto es mentira eso es mentira yo
lie what I
no lo escuché esto est mentira lo que
heard is that if she was right in
escuché es que si se la tuviera de
front of me that she was coming to Barcelona there would be a
frente que venía a Barcelona habría un
quick trial but it is not known why there would be
juicio rápido pero no se sabe por qué
a quick trial Oh surprise she didn't
habría un juicio rápido Ah sorpresa no
threaten him eh she didn't threaten her she didn't
lo amenazó eh no la amenazó no la
threaten her eh Oh surprise what she said
amenazó eh Ah sorpresa lo que le dijo
was that if he crossed her there would be a
fue que si se la cruzaba habría un
trial  quick but eh It is not known
juicio rápido pero eh No se sabe el Por
why it could be for stealing a vest
qué podría ser por robar un chaleco
it could be for stealing a
podría ser por robar un
candy it could be for a
caramelo podría ser por un accidente de
traffic accident s for insults eh Why did I not
tráfico s por insultos eh Por qué yo no
hear that he was going to shave her hair no no
escuché que la iba a rasar los pelos no
no with which we do not increase okay let's not
no no con lo cual no aumentemos vale no
invent like I find her the
inventemos como yo me la encuentro la
p let's go to that one I grab her by the Bow but I track her
p vamos a esa la cojo del Moño pero la
but I track well take
rastreo pero bien rastrea toma
Tania take Tania and make her talk about her [ __ ]
Tania toma Tania y que hable de su [__]
mother take Tania defend your daughter defi
madre toma Tania defiende tu hija defi
you Ah that Tania you are the
tu Ah eso Tania que eres la
best I wanted to see
mejor quería ver
here we have the explanation of everything
aquí tenemos la explicación de todo
look for example
mira por ejemplo
this Look what he said this is one of
este Mirad lo que decía este es uno de
those who took the clips so that I
los que me cogía los clips para que yo
could do it directly reacting to Peppa
hiciera directo reaccionando a la Peppa
okay Look what he said at that moment
vale Mirad lo que decía en ese momento
eh I mean this is what he
eh o sea esto es lo que él
truly thinks I
verdaderamente piensa
understand it does not harm me at all I am me I am
entiendo a mí no me perjudica nada Yo
not the one who kept 240
soy yo no soy el que me quedé con 240
euros for 6 months that were going to a foundation
eur por 6 meses que iban a una fundación
against
contra el
cancer okay This is what he thinks
cáncer vale Esto es lo que piensa él
about the 240 issue until
sobre el tema de los 240 hasta que
Loli appeared and did this
apareció Loli y le hizo este chorreo de
Uncle Loli drip  She buys them and lets herself be bought That's it, there's no
Tío Loli los compra y se dejan comprar
more, there's no more Look, I
Ya está no hay más no hay más Mira yo no
'm not the one who kept 240 for 6
soy el que me quedé con 240 por 6
months and now why are you with her,
meses y ahora por qué estás con ella por
why are you defending her now, man,
qué la defiendes ahora tío
and I don't take money from an
y yo no le saco dinero a una señora
elderly lady who is not in good
mayor que no está bien de
health, well now yes
salud pues ahora
Now yes, Loli Huertas supports my
sí Ahora sí Loli huertas apoya a mi
family economy 54 pesos with 40
economía familiar 54 pesos con 40
cents, she tried to get me to pay her
centavos ella intentó que pagándole
200,000 and she wouldn't sue me, haha, and for
200000 e no me demandaba jaj y por lo
criminal reasons, haha I piss myself
penal ja Yo me meo
Ah, so in the end it was all money, money money,
Ah o sea a fin de cuentas todo era money
everything was Money, everything was money I
money money todo era Money todo era
mean, in the end it was all Money
O sea a fin de cuentas todo era Money
Loli, everything was
Loli todo era
Money, apparently
Money por lo que se ve
200,000 and no, no, I also wanted some
200.000 y no no quería también unos
refried beans with
refritos con un agua de
Jamaican water, a delivery of Did Food, something, something
Jamaica un envío de did Food algo algo
else, Loli asked you for it, or was it wrong, the 20,000
más te pedía Loli o lo mal los 20.000
Thanks for the sub How much was the
Gracias por el sub De cuánto fue el
super chat Loli, I didn't see it Sorry Oh
super chat Loli que no lo vi Perdón Ay
Loli, please I'm realizing the
Loli por favor me estoy dando cuenta del
Super chat 50 Thanks Loli, it wasn't
Super chat 50 Gracias Loli no hacía
necessary Loli  That amount was not necessary
falta Loli no hacía falta esa cantidad
but thank you very much eh Just now I
pero muchas gracias eh Hasta ahorita me
'm realizing eh from the Super chat I did
estoy dando cuenta eh del Super chat yo
n't see it I didn't see it How much was it I already saw the
no lo vi no lo vi De cuánto era ya vi el
color I said this color I haven't seen it very
color dije este color no lo he visto muy
often and I already read Thank you very much Loli for
seguido y ya le Muchas gracias Loli por
the super chat it's tremendous I didn't
el super chat está tremendo no lo
need to send it so so so big Thank you very much
ocupaba mandar tan tan tan grande Muchas
200,000 She's asking you for
gracias 200.000 Te está pidiendo
200,000 she's asking for sol she's going to have to
200.000 le está pidiendo sol los va a
pay them because Loli I find it
tener que pagar porque es que Loli veo
very complicated that they don't condemn her
muy complicado que no la conden
eh Hey guys I have to go eh it's
eh Oye chicos ya me tengo que ir eh son
less 10 I have it at 5
menos 10 lo tengo a las 5 ya va a estar
the coach will be around here appearing eh
por aquí apareciendo el entrenador eh
[Music]
[Música]
Ah there was a live on the subject of
Ah hubo directo sobre el tema de la
Loli there was Ah well look you see I
Loli hubo Ah pues mira fíjate tú que yo
thought that no one did a live on
me creía que ninguno hizo directo sobre
the subject of Loli let's
el tema de la Loli a
see indiscreet she's talking about the subject right
ver indiscreta está hablando del tema de
now she has 600 people about what
ahora mismo tiene 600 personas de lo que
happened yesterday with with the lady She
pasó ayer con con la señora
lost her wig
Se ha perdido la peluca
do not
no
show provocation and I have not been
demostrar provocación y yo no he sido
brutal the same person has been against me for a long time
brutala misma persona est hace mucho
also brutally I don't know  can
contra m tambi brutalmente no se puede
do that having a camera in
hacer eso teniendo una cámara
front provoked provoke way if Tom
delante provocado provocan manera si Tom
agu with
agu con
serious affection vitamin B that they
serio cariño vitamina B que a mí me
tell me tremendous things and I don't go out like that
dicen cosas tremendas y yo no salgo así
Who is the one that is called and one
Quién es la que están llamada y le una
for me was my
para mí era mi
friend my friend and we talked almost every
amiga mi amiga y hablábamos casi todos
day she said that she was horrible and she is
los días decía que era horrible y está
with them licking her ass like
con ellos lamiéndole el culo como lo
other people are Peppa very
están otras personas Peppa muy
rude and they are with her licking her
grosera y están con ella lamiéndole el
ass like other people are I mean
culo como le están otras personas o sea
Peppa is calling
Peppa está llamando
those who are with Loli are with
a los a los que estén con Loli están con
her for licking her
ella por lle el
ass and I can assure you and the other one that I
culo y te puedo asegurar y la otra que
also thought was my friend well
también creí que era mi amiga pues que
[ __ ] the two of them the journalist
le den morcillas a los dos la periodista
Joana and the other one but the other one and the other one
la Joana y al otro pero a la otra y al
and the one on the motorcycle that I don't care so
otro y al de la moto que me da igual
much friendship has been friends for two days
tanta amistad lleva dos días de
how strong
amistad qué fuerte
No how strong no And this one
No qué fuerte no Y esta
continues But why is she seeing she is
sigue Pero para qué está viendo está
seeing the same thing she is
viendo lo mismo
not seeing the debate that I had with
no está viendo el debate que tuve con
her but
ella pero para
why each one with his own issue guys I am
qué cada uno con su tema chicos me me me
freaking out Hey look Well look
quedado flipando Oye mira Pues mira
someone opened live to report the
alguien abrió directo para denunciar el
issue of what Loli did the other day
tema de de lo que hizo Loli el otro día
Okay  I thought that nobody but
Está bien me creía que nadie per nada
nothing more than I saw that they kept
más que nada más que veía que seguían
talking about whether I'm
hablando de si yo me
wrong oh my goodness oh
equivoco madre
my goodness guys well I'm going to the gym the
mía chicos pues me voy al gimnasio la
truth is that with a little laziness eh today I
verdad que con un poco de pereza eh hoy
woke up exhausted man today I woke up exhausted exhausted exhausted
me he levantado reventados tío hoy me he
man today I'm [ __ ] man
reventados tío hoy estoy cago tío
today I'm [ __ ] and I have to do a
hoy estoy cao y tengo que hacer un
lot of things now in the afternoon
montón de cosas ahora por la tarde
man I don't know what I'll do man I don't know if at
tío no sé qué haré tío No sé si por la
night I'm going to come and I'm going to do a live
noche voy a venir y voy a hacer directo
here
aquí
or I'm going to prepare a good video
en o me voy a preparar un buen vídeo
for the
para el
main one I don't know what I'll do man It's that
principal no sé qué haré tío
the salsera Well I don't know German I don't
que la salsería Pues no lo sé Germán no
know if things are right or
sé si sán cosas o
not but the truth is I would like it is that I don't
no pero la verdad me gustaría es que no
know I would like to make a good video on the
sé me gustaría hacer un buen vídeo en el
main channel of these ones of mine
canal principal de estos de los míos
about the subject of Dana about the subject
sobre el tema de la Dana sobre el tema
of how it has been mismanaged but I do
de de cómo se ha gestionado de mal pero
n't know if I'm
no sé si voy
late I don't know if I'm late man do you think I'm
tarde no sé si voy tarde tío creéis que
late or we still have time to
voy tarde o todavía estamos a tiempo de
do it
hacerlo
Today there's Horizonte
Hoy hay Horizonte
already but I don't know if I'm going to be able to watch it
ya pero no sé si lo voy a poder ver en
live it's that if I watch it I don't
directo es que si lo veo no
work a little  sugar no No look today I
trabajo un poco de azúcar no No mira hoy
drank a monster that I
me he bebido un monster que que lo
was quitting and I can't quit
estaba dejando y no consigo dejarlo
because in the end I always go crazy I always go
porque al final siempre voy loco Siempre
busted well I'll probably do it
voy reventado pues Probablemente lo haga
eh in the end yes you're going to do it it's
eh al final sí lo vas a hacer es
better everyday but it's it's it's it's
que mejor cotidi pero es
what are we going to do
que es que es que de qué vamos a hacer
live today if the issues of the heart
directo hoy si los temas del corazón
have stopped too well I prepare
está han parado también pues me preparo
a good video no and we do a good
un buen vídeo no y hacemos un buen
job No that I feel that I feel that a
trabajo No que adás siento que siento
good video is needed a good
que hace falta un buen vídeo un buen
video on YouTube that comments on everything and that
vídeo en YouTube que comente todo y que
exp puts everything well Pin Pin Pin it's not
exp ponga todo bien Pin Pin Pin no es
late but it's complicated eh
tarde pero es complicado
I think it can be eh I think it could be ha
eh yo creo que se puede eh yo creo que
I think it could be
ha yo creo que se podría ser
a good video of this with with little things
un buen vídeo de esto con con cositas
with little things a good video but a
con cositas un buen vídeo pero de los
good one a good video but a good one
buenos un buen vídeo pero de los buenos
for that you have to go to the focus of the
para eso hay que ir al foco de la
news but Auri is that Ah is ah the
noticia pero Auri es que Ah está ah el
coach guys I'm going a kiss a kiss
entrenador chicos me voy un beso un beso
handsome
guapos
[Music]
[Música]